<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Tabs</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tabs on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/action_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/action_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page has three report types. Time per action and Timesheet for actions appear only if the option for Time registration for actions is activated. In all three reports, you can click on the name or number of the action to open it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-matrix&#34;&gt;Action matrix&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report that shows the status for all open actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The colour codes for the status are shown above the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the name of an action to open it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used together with the option for start time for actions, this report can be used to give an overview of the planned actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The overview starts 3 days before today&amp;rsquo;s date and includes the next 26 days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The transition from today&amp;rsquo;s date to the next day is marked with a vertical black line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The matrix is sorted by the action&amp;rsquo;s start date, if this is set. If not, the date the action was registered is used instead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;time-per-action&#34;&gt;Time per action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report that shows how much time has been registered on all actions in the selected period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions without any registered time are not included in the report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The report includes actions registered on or below the department currently selected in the navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shows per user and total.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The actions are ordered by action number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This report is only available when the option for time registration on actions is activated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;timesheet-for-actions&#34;&gt;Timesheet for actions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report that shows how much time, in the selected period, has been registered per action per user per day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sums per day per user and total for all users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This report is only available when the option for time registration on actions is activated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Comment reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/comment_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/comment_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The graphs for the comment messages are shown here.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Message reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/message_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/message_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The graphs for common messages are shown here. If you have done a search, you can click on this tab to reset all the search criteria.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Graph-search.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;




      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Risk reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/risk_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/risk_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The graphs for the risk messages are shown here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tab appears only if the risk messages are enabled.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Search graphs</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/search_graph/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/search_graph/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;It opens the search page for messages or the search page for actions depending on which tab you were under.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: User reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/user_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/user_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Provides an overview of the logins and the document usage in the system in a given period of time. The overview depends on the selected report, the report type, the time frame and the period type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search: Updates the report with the selected time frame.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report for logins.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report for document usage. Shows data for documents that have been opened, regardless of the page they were opened from (Info, Admin, Register new message or external use).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report type
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When &amp;ldquo;Report for logins&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Login overview: Shows all the logins in a given period. The table can be sorted by Name (default) or Time, by clicking on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Login overview distributed over time: Shows the number of logins per user per period. The table is sorted by name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Login data distributed over time: Shows the number of logins per period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Average values for the period: Shows the average number of logins per period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When &amp;ldquo;Report for document usage&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents per user: Shows all the documents and the user who has opened them in a given period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents per user over time: Shows how many documents each user has opened in each period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Users per document over time: Shows how many users have opened each document in each period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents over time: Shows how many documents have been opened in total in each period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Average values for the period: Shows how many documents have been opened in average in each period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Period type
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Month&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Max 1000 rows are displayed in the table regardless of choice.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
