<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Functions</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/functions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Functions on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/functions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit document data</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/functions/edit_document_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/functions/edit_document_data/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes0hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a super user / manager I can add new documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can choose whether the document will be retrieved from my own database: Click &amp;ldquo;Link&amp;rdquo;, or from a file: CliCk &amp;ldquo;File&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Or I can write a document in the internal editor. Click on the tab &amp;ldquo;Document content&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Document data: Used to edit the general information relating to a document. This is the first page you see when you create a new document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Document content: Shows only for internal documents (document type: &amp;ldquo;Write a document&amp;rdquo;). Used if you wish to write or edit a document directly in Qm+. The document is saved as an HTML document and has some formatting options. The text edit field uses TinyMCE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Shape_align_center.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Process chart setup: Shows only when the document type &amp;ldquo;Process chart&amp;rdquo; is selected and the document has been saved at least once. Used to define the various fields in a process chart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Role overview: Used to attach roles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder_link.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Version overview: Shows the overview of all versions, with the document at the current time, when it was changed and who made the change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Telephone_link.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Hearing / Approval: Used to create a new hearing and decide who will participate and approve it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Date.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Read and understood: Shows an overview of the status of all Read and understood activities the document has had.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_code.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Audit overview: Shows an overview of all the audits the document has had.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Image_link.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Reference overview: Shows an overview of all the references for the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Disc_multiple.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create new version: Creates a new version of the document.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Example: If a document is in version 3.14 and you click on this button, it will change version to 4.1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be used before making major changes to the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shows only for documents that have been saved at least once.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Disc.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes made in the fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit document group</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/functions/edit_document_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/functions/edit_document_group/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: The name of a document group can be registered once for every language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: The name of the document group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Column: Not specified (default), Left column, Right column. If the left or the right column is selected, the group will always appear at that position under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position: The position of the document group under Info. In the standard version two document groups are displayed side by side. The next two will appear below these again until all the document groups are displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: The document group will appear under Info from the selected department and from its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shown for subdepartments: If no, the document group will only appear under Info when the department selected under &amp;ldquo;From department&amp;rdquo; is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Starts closed under Info: No (default), Yes. If a group starts as closed, the user will have to click on it with the mouse in order to see the documents that are in it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background colour: If you want a special background colour for the document group, you can select it here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes made in the fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Color_wheel.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Choose colour: Opens a list of colors you can choose from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit document tab</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/functions/edit_document_tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/functions/edit_document_tab/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: The name of a document tab can be registered once for every language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: Used to identify the document tab in tables and overviews. A document tab can have one name for each language that is activated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position: The position of the document tab under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: The document tab will appear under Info from the selected department and from its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shown for subdepartments: If no, the document tab will only appear under Info when the department selected under &amp;ldquo;From department&amp;rdquo; is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subtab of: Used, if this tab should be a subtab. Then it will appear as a new level of tabs, under the tab that is selected here. Tabs with underlying tabs are not allowed to have their own documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information: Text that appears when you hold the cursor over the tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Role overview: A document tab with roles is only shown under Info if the user opening Info or the selected department in the navigator has at least one of the roles the document tab has.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes made in the fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;laquo; Add: Adds the selected role to this document tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove &amp;raquo;: Removes the selected role from this document tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
