<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Tabs</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tabs on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action process</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/action_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/action_process/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The possibility to make changes in this page depends on the user&amp;rsquo;s access to the relevant action. See Access control for actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-data&#34;&gt;Action data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action number: A unique number for each action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action name: Used to identify the action in tables and overviews. Mandatory field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered on department: The department on which the action is registered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start time: Does not show in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be finished before: Due date for the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Budget: How much is allocated to the implementation of the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual cost: How much was spent on the execution of the action. This field is used for calculating the cost graph for the action under Reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Planned time:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual time:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-description&#34;&gt;Action description&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Original deviation: Copied from the first text field in the original message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work description: Copied from the second text field in the original message. Should often be changed to a concrete task for those who will execute the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to prevent repetition: Copied from a possible third text field in the original message. Here you can write a little about other changes than the one that must be executed in this action, so that the original deviation will not happen again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment: Additional comments to the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-categories&#34;&gt;Action categories&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used for categorizing the action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;status&#34;&gt;Status&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This panel indicates where the action is in the action process. It partly controls the appearance of the rest of this screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under planning: All actions start with this status. In this phase, the action is being planned. First give a name to the action so that it becomes easy to identify it later, and enter the budget if you use this field. The text fields Corrective action and How to prevent repetition must be filled out so that those who will execute the action will know what to do. The action categories may also be selected now. The last thing is to select those who should execute the action and give them a deadline. This is done in the mandatory panel Persons responsible. Click on Send to execution &amp;raquo; or the &amp;raquo; button in the Status panel to save the action and change its status to Under execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under execution: In this phase, the work described in the action will be executed. Then those who carried out the action must tick the Executed box. They can also write a comment in the Comment field and fill in the Actual cost if they know it. When all the changes have been done, use the button Send to approval &amp;raquo; or the &amp;raquo; button in the Status panel. This saves the action and changes its status to Under approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under approval: Here the person who created the action will make sure everything is in order before (s)he approves the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approved: An approved action is closed and locked and can not be changed except by users with the system role content administrator. Comments can still be sent out to all involved users .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;persons-responsible&#34;&gt;Persons responsible&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shows an overview of all who have been involved in the case. They all have a checkbox next to their name that is used if you wish to send a message by email to some of these people with regard to this case. All sent messages will also appear at the bottom of this screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message originator: The users who have created messages attached to this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action was created by: The user who created the action and thus is responsible for it. Must approve the action before it is closed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action will be executed by: Those who will execute the action.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executed: This must be checked when the action has been performed (finished).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executed on / Hours spent: If time registration is enabled, the action executor can log his / her work here, by setting a date and filling in the hours field (decimal values accepted), and then clicking Save.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work log: If time registration is enabled, each time the Save button is clicked above, the logged hours appear here. You cannot add multiple entries for the same day, but you can always edit the existing entry for a specific date by clicking on it (the fields are editable).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action will be approved by: The person who will approve the action. In the standard version it is always the same user who created the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;case-history&#34;&gt;Case history&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Displays an overview of events for this action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All edits of the content or status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attachment or detachment of messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All sent out email comments attached to this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports from which you can export the current action to a .pdf file. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete action: Deletes the action. Appears only for the user who has created the action as long as it still has status Under planning, and for Content administrators. Deleted actions cannot be restored or found again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save action: Saves the changes you have made. Remember that this button never changes the Status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Send: Appears when you do not have permission to make changes in the action. Used to send email comments related to the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Returns you to the page you came from, unless you were in a message and created an action. Then you will go to where you opened this message from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Calendar_icon.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Calendar: Opens the calendar to select the date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Attached messages: Displays the messages attached to this action. Possibility to attach and detach more messages and to delete the action, for users who have the right to do it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action process: Reloads this page. All changes you have made without pressing the Save button afterwards will be lost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action search</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/search/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page is used for searching among registered actions. In many cases it is more appropriate to use Reports to identify specific actions than to use this page, but this page gives more options. This page can also be used together with Reports via the Expand search button in the search results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;general-search-criteria&#34;&gt;General search criteria&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;fields-that-use-data-from-the-actions&#34;&gt;Fields that use data from the actions&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time frame: From and To date fields (inclusive).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Include actions with the selected status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action number: Search for the action with this number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;fields-that-use-data-from-the-attached-messages&#34;&gt;Fields that use data from the attached messages&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: Include actions with the selected priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form type: Appears only if the Log messages or the Risk messages are activated. Include actions attached to messages with the selected form type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form: If you select something other than &amp;ldquo;All&amp;rdquo; here, the category groups and the categories in the section &amp;ldquo;Type of category to search by&amp;rdquo; below will only show those that are in use in the selected message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message number: Search for actions attached to the message with the selected message number. When this field is used, none of the other search criteria is used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Content search: Search for messages containing a given text. The text can be in any of the text fields in the message. Characters are not case sensitive. Lucene is the search engine used for this function. See Lucene Query Syntax for detailed information about the syntax for the search field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show messages from:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This department: Only messages registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This and subordinate departments: All messages registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator and on its subordinate departments are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subordinate departments: Only messages registered on the subordinate departments of the one which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show actions that are: Both options include actions from the selected department in the Navigator and from its subordinate departments.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created on selected departments: The department where the action was created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Processed by persons in the selected departments: The department where the action will be executed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Risk: Show the actions attached to messages with categories of the category group type Risk. Choose the P and C value for the messages that will be used.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P: Probability. Value from 0 - 5. 0 means that this parameter will not be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C: Consequence. Value from 0 - 5. 0 means that this parameter will not be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;type-of-category-to-search-by&#34;&gt;Type of category to search by&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the parameters in this section are used for the messages attached to the actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This section is used to search for category groups and categories. Check one or more category groups and / or select categories from the menus. The defining category groups appear at the top. Among them you can only search for one category group and / or category. If a message type or a message form is selected, only the category groups and the categories used in these message forms will appear in this section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;order-by&#34;&gt;Order by&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select the column by which the result table will be sorted.
Show results in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Table: Show the results in the table of the Search results page for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanded view: Show the results in the expanded view that contains all the action details (previously &amp;ldquo;Printer friendly&amp;rdquo; version) of the Search results page for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graph: Show the result as a chart under Reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action search results</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/action_search_results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/action_search_results/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page displays the results when performing an action search and when someone has clicked on an action graph under Reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;search-criteria&#34;&gt;Search criteria&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Displays all the parameters that are used for the search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The drop-down menu for the departments can be used to change the departments from which the actions will be retrieved from. The Navigator can be used to change the department or the department and its subordinate departments from which the actions will be retrieved, depending on what you have selected in the drop-down menu for departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The New search button clears all the search parameters except from the department which is selected in the Navigator and opens the search page for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Expand search button opens the search page for actions with all the parameters listed above in the search criteria list set. You should use this button if you want to continue working with the current search.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphs: 2 drop-down menus that can be used to change the content or focus of the search and display the result under Reports.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reports: Used to select the graph report type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category groups: The graph depends on the selected graph report type. When Per department / Per category and Per category / category group are selected, the graph shows an overview of the categories that belong to the selected category group. For the other graph report types, only actions with attached messages with checked categories of the selected category group are included in the graph.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search: This button opens the Reports with the parameters set in this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use of the table is explained in Actions.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Actions</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/actions/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Shows all the actions registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator with the status that is selected in one of the underlying tabs. If the underlying tabs have one action for every status, an additional tab for search appears. When performing a search from Action search, the selected search criteria are shown in a separate table above the results table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By clicking on a line in the main table, the action will open in the Action process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about an action, including its history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Expanded view / 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Table.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Table: Toggle between table and expanded view. The table gives a compact description of the actions intended for use when working with them. The expanded view gives a more complete description of the whole action, similar to the printer friendly (.pdf) version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/LeftArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Change page: The arrows are used to change the page when there are more than 20 cases that can be displayed in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Sorting: The table is sorted by the column with the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to sort by another column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_save.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save as file: Allows you to download and save the page as an HTML file on your machine locally. The file can be edited in any application that can edit HTML, including Word.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports, from which you can create a report with the related actions. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tabs here are used for choosing which status you wish to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under planning: Actions that have not been initiated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under execution: Actions that have been assigned to a person responsible for executing them and have been initiated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under approval: Executed actions that are pending approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approved actions: Approved actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search: Advanced search for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Attached messages</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/attached_messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/attached_messages/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Several messages can be attached to or detached from the action. Approved actions can not be attached to several messages or detached from messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;messages-attached-to-this-action&#34;&gt;Messages attached to this action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A table showing messages attached to this action. There must always be at least one message connected to an action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about a message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the Show message icon Application form magnify.png in the last column in order to look at or edit a message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the Detach message icon Application form delete.png to detach the selected message from the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;messages-that-are-not-closed&#34;&gt;Messages that are not closed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A table showing the open messages that are not attached to this action. Above the table are some search options, so that not all the open messages are shown at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select a category group: Here you can select criteria so that the messages shown in the table below will be similar to the ones that are already attached to this action.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining category: The message must have have the same defining category checked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;Category group name&gt;: The message must have the same category of the selected category group checked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any category: The message must have the same category checked in at least one category group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity: The message must be a comment message to the same activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List element: The message must be a comment message to the same question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show messages from this and subordinate departments
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes: Messages from this and the subordinate departments will be included in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No: Only messages from this department will be included in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search: Click on this when you have made the selection in the fields above to update the table below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about a message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the Show message icon Application form magnify.png in the last column in order to look at or edit a message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the Attach message icon Application form add.png to attach the selected message to the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;delete-action&#34;&gt;Delete action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Button that appears only for users with the system role content administrator. Detaches all messages from this action and deletes the action. Messages attached to other open actions get the status Action process. Messages only attached to other closed actions get the status Closed. Messages not attached to other actions get the status New.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action process: Opens the Action process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached messages: Reloads this screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
