<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Actions</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Actions on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/action/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/action/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Managed under Action process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usually created from the Message process page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can be deleted and get attached to or detached from messages under Attached messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action name: Used to identify the action in tables and overviews. Mandatory field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Budget: How much money is set aside for this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual cost: Describes what the actual cost was. This field is used as the cost field in the report for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Under planning, under execution, under approval, approved. See Action status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action categories: The categories of the type Action in the message this action was made for, can be used in the action to categorize it. This is a multiple choice field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;text-fields&#34;&gt;Text fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Original deviation: Description of the original deviation. Copied from the first text field in the message this action was created from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corrective action: Description of the corrective action. Option: May be copied from the second text field in the message this action was created from. The text copied here should often be interpreted as a suggestion and should be changed by the creator of the action to become a task description.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to prevent repetition: Description of how to prevent the incident from happening again. You have to do something more than simply correct the error. Option: May be copied from any third text field in the message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment: Additional comments to the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;persons-responsible&#34;&gt;Persons responsible&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message originator: The users who have created messages attached to this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action was created by: The user who created and owns the action and thus is responsible for it. Must also approve the action before it is closed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action will be executed by: Those who will execute the action. Can be selected among all the users in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action will be approved by: The person who will approve the action. It is always the same user who created the action. Can also be done by a super user with the system role Content administrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;access-control&#34;&gt;Access control&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All actions are registered on a department and get the status Under planning or Under execution if the selection of the executor is made in the Message process page. What kind of access a user has to an action is determined by the status and department of the action, and the user type, the department and the roles of the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-different-access-types-give-the-following-rights&#34;&gt;The different access types give the following rights&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can read the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can send email comments to it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can edit the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some fields require also Process access to be able to edit them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activates the Save button.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute for yourself
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can mark an action as Executed for their own users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute for others
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can mark an action as Executed for users within their own hierarchy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With Process access, can mark the action as Executed for users outside their own hierarchy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can process the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can change its status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can assign or remove the person responsible for execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can attach the action to several messages or detach it from messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can edit the field Original deviation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delete access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can delete the action. All attached messages will be detached and get the status New or Sent to case handler depending on their previous status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Administration access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can edit an action even if it is closed and locked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can re-open closed actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can also do whatever the other access types can do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;requirements-for-obtaining-the-various-access-types&#34;&gt;Requirements for obtaining the various access types&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read access
-The message originator of a message which is attached to the action.
-The executor of the action.
-Users with the user type manager, case handler or reviewer who have the same department as the one on which the action is registered or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.
-Users with the user type manager, case handler or reviewer who have the same department as the one on which a message attached to the action is registered or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.
-Users who have been set as case handlers for a message which is attached to this action.
-Users with the user type manager, case handler or reviewer who have the same department as a user who has been the case handler for a message attached to the action or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.
-Users who have been informed of a message through an email from the Message process page and this message is attached to the action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Write access is granted only when the action&amp;rsquo;s status is not Approved.
-Users with the user type manager or case handler who have the same department as the one on which the action is registered or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.
-Users who will execute the action and the action&amp;rsquo;s status is Under execution.
-Users with the user type manager or case handler who have the same department as the action&amp;rsquo;s executors or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Execute for yourself
-Users who will execute the action and the action&amp;rsquo;s status is Under execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Execute for others
-Users with the user type manager or case handler who have the same department as the action&amp;rsquo;s executors or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy, and the action&amp;rsquo;s status is Under execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Process access
-Users with the user type manager or case handler who have the same department as the one on which the action is registered or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delete access
-The owner of the action, the user who will approve the action, can delete it if it has the status Under planning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Administration access
-Given to the users with the system role Content Administrator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action search</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/search/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page is used for searching among registered actions. In many cases it is more appropriate to use Reports to identify specific actions than to use this page, but this page gives more options. This page can also be used together with Reports via the Expand search button in the search results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;general-search-criteria&#34;&gt;General search criteria&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;fields-that-use-data-from-the-actions&#34;&gt;Fields that use data from the actions&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time frame: From and To date fields (inclusive).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Include actions with the selected status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action number: Search for the action with this number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;fields-that-use-data-from-the-attached-messages&#34;&gt;Fields that use data from the attached messages&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: Include actions with the selected priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form type: Appears only if the Log messages or the Risk messages are activated. Include actions attached to messages with the selected form type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form: If you select something other than &amp;ldquo;All&amp;rdquo; here, the category groups and the categories in the section &amp;ldquo;Type of category to search by&amp;rdquo; below will only show those that are in use in the selected message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message number: Search for actions attached to the message with the selected message number. When this field is used, none of the other search criteria is used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Content search: Search for messages containing a given text. The text can be in any of the text fields in the message. Characters are not case sensitive. Lucene is the search engine used for this function. See Lucene Query Syntax for detailed information about the syntax for the search field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show messages from:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This department: Only messages registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This and subordinate departments: All messages registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator and on its subordinate departments are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subordinate departments: Only messages registered on the subordinate departments of the one which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show actions that are: Both options include actions from the selected department in the Navigator and from its subordinate departments.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created on selected departments: The department where the action was created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Processed by persons in the selected departments: The department where the action will be executed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Risk: Show the actions attached to messages with categories of the category group type Risk. Choose the P and C value for the messages that will be used.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P: Probability. Value from 0 - 5. 0 means that this parameter will not be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C: Consequence. Value from 0 - 5. 0 means that this parameter will not be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;type-of-category-to-search-by&#34;&gt;Type of category to search by&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the parameters in this section are used for the messages attached to the actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This section is used to search for category groups and categories. Check one or more category groups and / or select categories from the menus. The defining category groups appear at the top. Among them you can only search for one category group and / or category. If a message type or a message form is selected, only the category groups and the categories used in these message forms will appear in this section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;order-by&#34;&gt;Order by&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select the column by which the result table will be sorted.
Show results in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Table: Show the results in the table of the Search results page for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanded view: Show the results in the expanded view that contains all the action details (previously &amp;ldquo;Printer friendly&amp;rdquo; version) of the Search results page for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graph: Show the result as a chart under Reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Tabs</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;All tabs associated with actions.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
