<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Functions</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Functions on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Do you have comments?</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/do_you_have_comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/do_you_have_comments/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;It is only possible to register one comment message per question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Back to list: Sends you back to Filling out a list form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Done: Sends you back to Fill out and results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the Edit message form to write a new comment message on the question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the Edit message form to edit a comment message on the question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit list content</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/edit_list_content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/edit_list_content/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Available from Checklists, Risk analysis lists and Survey forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Displays a list of all the topics and questions that are included in the list. Topics have a dark yellow background, questions are light yellow and the selected element is red. Click on the text of a topic or question to select it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the list has been answered, it will not be possible to make any more changes other than sorting. Make a copy of the list if you wish to change it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode-s0-hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can add questions in a survey form. Recommendation: Divide the questions into topics. Click on the &amp;ldquo;New topic&amp;rdquo; icon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can add questions under each topic. Click on the &amp;ldquo;Add question&amp;rdquo; icon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can also explain the background of the question. Click on the yellow pencil icon, and write the text in the text field that appears.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can select alternative answers. Click on the button: &amp;ldquo;Edit alternative answers&amp;rdquo;. Then a new page will open.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menu&#34;&gt;Drop-down menu&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language: All the text fields in a list can be entered once for every language that is activated. When filling out the list, it will be shown to the user in the language (s)he has chosen. If the list was not created for that language, it will be shown in the language it was made.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_gear.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit list information. Takes you to the Edit list information screen to edit the information on the selected checklist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_key.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit alternative answers. Takes you to the Edit alternative answers screen to edit the content of the selected list. It is only possible to edit alternative answers in survey forms that were created on the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Preview. Opens the preview window to see how the list looks in the printer friendly version. In this window you can also choose to see the list in list form or as a series of single questions which is how it will look when it will be filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes the Edit list content page and takes you back to the page you came from (Checklists, Risk analysis lists or Survey forms).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Accept.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Accept: Saves the changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Cancel: Cancels the changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Layout_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New topic: Opens a text field where a new topic with comments can be entered. The topic is placed below the row with the icon that you clicked on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Add question: Opens a text field where a new question with comments can be entered. The new question is placed under the selected question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Pencil.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit: Opens a text field to edit the selected topic or question. It also opens a text field wherever a comment text on a selected topic or question can be entered. This comment will be displayed when the list will be filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Layout_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete topic: When a topic is deleted, all the questions in this topic are also deleted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete: Deletes the selected question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrow_down.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrow_up.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Sorting: Arrows move topics and questions a notch in the direction of the arrow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Export to the common library</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/export_to_common_library/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/export_to_common_library/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;List name: The name that will appear in the common library. The original name of the exported form is set as default.
Information: Additional information field.
Select description tags: Check the words that describe what you are exporting or the general area for it. Contact drift@qmplus.com if the required word or phrase is missing. These words can be used to search for forms in the common library.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_go.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Export: Performs the export to the common library and takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes this screen and takes you back to the page you came from. Nothing will be saved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Filling out a list form</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/filling_out_a_list_form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/filling_out_a_list_form/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;When the selected display type is the list version, or when the list is opened in order to be filled out when you are logged into Qm+ in the usual way, then the list opens in the list version view. This means that all questions are listed one after the other. There are no comment fields in the first page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The blue texts above the list are documents. Clicking on these opens a separate window with information that the person who has sent out the list thinks is relevant for those who should answer it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Checkboxes: Their appearance will vary depending on the list type. Check or make your choice for all the questions in the list that apply to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version history: Shown for lists that have been answered. Drop-down menu that shows who answered the list and when it was done. Choose one of the options in the drop-down menu to see what the answer looked like at that time. Note that the Save button only appears when the latest version is selected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the answer. If the list that you answer does not have any comment fields together with the questions, you will come to the page Do you have comments?. There you will have the opportunity to comment on all the questions you have checked in the list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Exits the answer without saving.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Filling out a list in single question view</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/filling_out_a_list_in_single_question_view/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/filling_out_a_list_in_single_question_view/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page is used when the display type single question view is selected and the list is opened from a link in an email sent out from Qm+. This means that all questions appear one by one with the comment field directly next to the question. When a question is answered, press &amp;ldquo;Next Question &amp;raquo;&amp;rdquo; to go to the next question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The blue texts above the list are documents. Clicking on these opens a separate window with information that the person who has sent out the list thinks is relevant for those who should answer it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Checkboxes: Their appearance will vary depending on the list type. Check or make your choice for all the questions in the list that apply to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment field: The title will vary depending on what was written by whoever created the list. For multiple choice questions there may be one comment field for each alternative answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hidden topics: In some cases, the person who has created the list has hidden some questions in some topics. This means that one must check the &amp;ldquo;Select&amp;rdquo; field after the name of the topic in order for the questions to appear. This is done so that it will be easy to skip questions that do not apply to the specific user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next question &amp;raquo;: Displays the next question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;laquo; Previous question: Displays the previous question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Save: Saves the answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Close: Closes this question without saving anything.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
