<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Qmplus documentation</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Qmplus documentation on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Consequence</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/other/consequence/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/other/consequence/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;To reduce the risk value one must initiate consequence-reducing measures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Example: Injury event. Possible consequence-reducing measures:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use of helmets on the construction site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First Aid kits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mandatory life vest when on a boat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scale of consequence in Qm+ is 1 - 5. The default values are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SET 1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insignificant damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Light damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Widespread damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alternatively, customers can define their own texts. These sets are also available and can be used by setting the system preference RISKSCALE. Please note that the same set number will be used for both probability and consequence unless a different set number is defined for Consequence in the SPAN field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SET 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Safe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dangerous&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Critical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very critical&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Catastrophic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SET 3&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cat 1&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cat 2&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cat 3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cat 4&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cat 5&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SET 4&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insignificant damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Light damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Widespread damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SET 5&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Negligible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moderate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Significant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Severe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Catastrophic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SET 6&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Insignificant damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Light damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Widespread damage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SET 7&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Little consequence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Middle consequence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Big consequence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Very big consequence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Catastrophic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Definitions</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/other/definitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/other/definitions/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Action plan = measures to correct errors or eliminate system errors in order to prevent recurrence
Adverse event (AE) = something more than a deviation, abbreviated to AE (or RAE = Registered AE)
Audit = control / comparison &amp;ldquo;live and learn&amp;rdquo;, with checklists and questions
Audit report = contains: minutes, reviewed topics, who conducted what, conclusions
Checklist = point-wise enumeration of conditions to be controlled
Contribute = employees must actively participate in the HES work, §§ 4 og 5.3
Control = comparison, synonymous with audit
Deviation = something missing, error in relation to written procedures. See adverse events.
Deviation message = form where deviations and proposals are registered
Deviation overview = graphs and tables that display all or a specific extract of deviation messages
Instructions = recommended procedure (most often when a person should do something)
Internal control (IC) = Own (self) control, synonymous term for quality management
Motivate = set in motion, - not to be confused with the desire to create feelings
Procedure = written procedure, description of a process in which many participate (From the Latin &amp;ldquo;procedere&amp;rdquo;: To show the order of execution and requirements for the execution of each phase (= Method), and who is involved in every phase with which responsibility)
Quality = Properties
Quality Management (QM) = a craft that requires active use of specific methods
Quality plan = includes all activities that are used for preventing errors
Responsibility = the ability to give answers when needed
Risk = probability x consequence
Routine = agreed procedure (oral)
System = when specified parts work together
System error = error that recurs, that happens because the system allows it
User survey = questionnaire answered by users, customers, relatives, etc.
Verify = check if it is true, from the Latin &amp;ldquo;Verus&amp;rdquo; = true, &amp;ldquo;facere&amp;rdquo; = make&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: List type</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/list_type/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/list_type/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Option page for documents</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/option_page_for_documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/option_page_for_documents/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Appears when you press the Show as pdf button from such a document in Info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;options&#34;&gt;Options&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the subdocuments: Select this option if you want the .pdf to include the contents of all the subdocuments of the selected document that are also written in Qm+. Preselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Only the main document: Select this option if you want the .pdf to contain only the selected document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create report: Creates the report with the selected options. Please note that you should not close this page before the report is ready, otherwise you will never see the report. After the new report opens, you can either change the selected options and create another report or simply close this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes the Option page for documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/action/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/action/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Managed under Action process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Usually created from the Message process page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can be deleted and get attached to or detached from messages under Attached messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action name: Used to identify the action in tables and overviews. Mandatory field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Budget: How much money is set aside for this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual cost: Describes what the actual cost was. This field is used as the cost field in the report for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Under planning, under execution, under approval, approved. See Action status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action categories: The categories of the type Action in the message this action was made for, can be used in the action to categorize it. This is a multiple choice field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;text-fields&#34;&gt;Text fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Original deviation: Description of the original deviation. Copied from the first text field in the message this action was created from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Corrective action: Description of the corrective action. Option: May be copied from the second text field in the message this action was created from. The text copied here should often be interpreted as a suggestion and should be changed by the creator of the action to become a task description.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to prevent repetition: Description of how to prevent the incident from happening again. You have to do something more than simply correct the error. Option: May be copied from any third text field in the message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment: Additional comments to the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;persons-responsible&#34;&gt;Persons responsible&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message originator: The users who have created messages attached to this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action was created by: The user who created and owns the action and thus is responsible for it. Must also approve the action before it is closed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action will be executed by: Those who will execute the action. Can be selected among all the users in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action will be approved by: The person who will approve the action. It is always the same user who created the action. Can also be done by a super user with the system role Content administrator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;access-control&#34;&gt;Access control&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All actions are registered on a department and get the status Under planning or Under execution if the selection of the executor is made in the Message process page. What kind of access a user has to an action is determined by the status and department of the action, and the user type, the department and the roles of the user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-different-access-types-give-the-following-rights&#34;&gt;The different access types give the following rights&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can read the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can send email comments to it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can edit the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some fields require also Process access to be able to edit them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activates the Save button.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute for yourself
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can mark an action as Executed for their own users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute for others
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can mark an action as Executed for users within their own hierarchy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With Process access, can mark the action as Executed for users outside their own hierarchy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can process the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can change its status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can assign or remove the person responsible for execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can attach the action to several messages or detach it from messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can edit the field Original deviation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delete access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can delete the action. All attached messages will be detached and get the status New or Sent to case handler depending on their previous status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Administration access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can edit an action even if it is closed and locked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can re-open closed actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can also do whatever the other access types can do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;requirements-for-obtaining-the-various-access-types&#34;&gt;Requirements for obtaining the various access types&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read access
-The message originator of a message which is attached to the action.
-The executor of the action.
-Users with the user type manager, case handler or reviewer who have the same department as the one on which the action is registered or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.
-Users with the user type manager, case handler or reviewer who have the same department as the one on which a message attached to the action is registered or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.
-Users who have been set as case handlers for a message which is attached to this action.
-Users with the user type manager, case handler or reviewer who have the same department as a user who has been the case handler for a message attached to the action or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.
-Users who have been informed of a message through an email from the Message process page and this message is attached to the action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Write access is granted only when the action&amp;rsquo;s status is not Approved.
-Users with the user type manager or case handler who have the same department as the one on which the action is registered or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.
-Users who will execute the action and the action&amp;rsquo;s status is Under execution.
-Users with the user type manager or case handler who have the same department as the action&amp;rsquo;s executors or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Execute for yourself
-Users who will execute the action and the action&amp;rsquo;s status is Under execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Execute for others
-Users with the user type manager or case handler who have the same department as the action&amp;rsquo;s executors or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy, and the action&amp;rsquo;s status is Under execution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Process access
-Users with the user type manager or case handler who have the same department as the one on which the action is registered or a department which is directly above this in the hierarchy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delete access
-The owner of the action, the user who will approve the action, can delete it if it has the status Under planning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Administration access
-Given to the users with the system role Content Administrator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action process</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/action_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/action_process/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The possibility to make changes in this page depends on the user&amp;rsquo;s access to the relevant action. See Access control for actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-data&#34;&gt;Action data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action number: A unique number for each action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action name: Used to identify the action in tables and overviews. Mandatory field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered on department: The department on which the action is registered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start time: Does not show in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be finished before: Due date for the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Budget: How much is allocated to the implementation of the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual cost: How much was spent on the execution of the action. This field is used for calculating the cost graph for the action under Reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Planned time:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actual time:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-description&#34;&gt;Action description&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Original deviation: Copied from the first text field in the original message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work description: Copied from the second text field in the original message. Should often be changed to a concrete task for those who will execute the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to prevent repetition: Copied from a possible third text field in the original message. Here you can write a little about other changes than the one that must be executed in this action, so that the original deviation will not happen again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment: Additional comments to the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-categories&#34;&gt;Action categories&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used for categorizing the action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;status&#34;&gt;Status&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This panel indicates where the action is in the action process. It partly controls the appearance of the rest of this screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under planning: All actions start with this status. In this phase, the action is being planned. First give a name to the action so that it becomes easy to identify it later, and enter the budget if you use this field. The text fields Corrective action and How to prevent repetition must be filled out so that those who will execute the action will know what to do. The action categories may also be selected now. The last thing is to select those who should execute the action and give them a deadline. This is done in the mandatory panel Persons responsible. Click on Send to execution &amp;raquo; or the &amp;raquo; button in the Status panel to save the action and change its status to Under execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under execution: In this phase, the work described in the action will be executed. Then those who carried out the action must tick the Executed box. They can also write a comment in the Comment field and fill in the Actual cost if they know it. When all the changes have been done, use the button Send to approval &amp;raquo; or the &amp;raquo; button in the Status panel. This saves the action and changes its status to Under approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under approval: Here the person who created the action will make sure everything is in order before (s)he approves the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approved: An approved action is closed and locked and can not be changed except by users with the system role content administrator. Comments can still be sent out to all involved users .&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;persons-responsible&#34;&gt;Persons responsible&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shows an overview of all who have been involved in the case. They all have a checkbox next to their name that is used if you wish to send a message by email to some of these people with regard to this case. All sent messages will also appear at the bottom of this screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message originator: The users who have created messages attached to this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action was created by: The user who created the action and thus is responsible for it. Must approve the action before it is closed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action will be executed by: Those who will execute the action.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executed: This must be checked when the action has been performed (finished).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executed on / Hours spent: If time registration is enabled, the action executor can log his / her work here, by setting a date and filling in the hours field (decimal values accepted), and then clicking Save.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work log: If time registration is enabled, each time the Save button is clicked above, the logged hours appear here. You cannot add multiple entries for the same day, but you can always edit the existing entry for a specific date by clicking on it (the fields are editable).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The action will be approved by: The person who will approve the action. In the standard version it is always the same user who created the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;case-history&#34;&gt;Case history&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Displays an overview of events for this action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All edits of the content or status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attachment or detachment of messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All sent out email comments attached to this action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports from which you can export the current action to a .pdf file. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete action: Deletes the action. Appears only for the user who has created the action as long as it still has status Under planning, and for Content administrators. Deleted actions cannot be restored or found again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save action: Saves the changes you have made. Remember that this button never changes the Status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Send: Appears when you do not have permission to make changes in the action. Used to send email comments related to the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Returns you to the page you came from, unless you were in a message and created an action. Then you will go to where you opened this message from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Calendar_icon.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Calendar: Opens the calendar to select the date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Attached messages: Displays the messages attached to this action. Possibility to attach and detach more messages and to delete the action, for users who have the right to do it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action process: Reloads this page. All changes you have made without pressing the Save button afterwards will be lost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/action_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/action_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page has three report types. Time per action and Timesheet for actions appear only if the option for Time registration for actions is activated. In all three reports, you can click on the name or number of the action to open it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;action-matrix&#34;&gt;Action matrix&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report that shows the status for all open actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The colour codes for the status are shown above the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the name of an action to open it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used together with the option for start time for actions, this report can be used to give an overview of the planned actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The overview starts 3 days before today&amp;rsquo;s date and includes the next 26 days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The transition from today&amp;rsquo;s date to the next day is marked with a vertical black line.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The matrix is sorted by the action&amp;rsquo;s start date, if this is set. If not, the date the action was registered is used instead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;time-per-action&#34;&gt;Time per action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report that shows how much time has been registered on all actions in the selected period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions without any registered time are not included in the report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The report includes actions registered on or below the department currently selected in the navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shows per user and total.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The actions are ordered by action number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This report is only available when the option for time registration on actions is activated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;timesheet-for-actions&#34;&gt;Timesheet for actions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report that shows how much time, in the selected period, has been registered per action per user per day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sums per day per user and total for all users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This report is only available when the option for time registration on actions is activated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action search</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/search/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page is used for searching among registered actions. In many cases it is more appropriate to use Reports to identify specific actions than to use this page, but this page gives more options. This page can also be used together with Reports via the Expand search button in the search results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;general-search-criteria&#34;&gt;General search criteria&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;fields-that-use-data-from-the-actions&#34;&gt;Fields that use data from the actions&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time frame: From and To date fields (inclusive).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Include actions with the selected status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action number: Search for the action with this number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;fields-that-use-data-from-the-attached-messages&#34;&gt;Fields that use data from the attached messages&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: Include actions with the selected priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form type: Appears only if the Log messages or the Risk messages are activated. Include actions attached to messages with the selected form type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form: If you select something other than &amp;ldquo;All&amp;rdquo; here, the category groups and the categories in the section &amp;ldquo;Type of category to search by&amp;rdquo; below will only show those that are in use in the selected message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message number: Search for actions attached to the message with the selected message number. When this field is used, none of the other search criteria is used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Content search: Search for messages containing a given text. The text can be in any of the text fields in the message. Characters are not case sensitive. Lucene is the search engine used for this function. See Lucene Query Syntax for detailed information about the syntax for the search field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show messages from:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This department: Only messages registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This and subordinate departments: All messages registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator and on its subordinate departments are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subordinate departments: Only messages registered on the subordinate departments of the one which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show actions that are: Both options include actions from the selected department in the Navigator and from its subordinate departments.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created on selected departments: The department where the action was created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Processed by persons in the selected departments: The department where the action will be executed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Risk: Show the actions attached to messages with categories of the category group type Risk. Choose the P and C value for the messages that will be used.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P: Probability. Value from 0 - 5. 0 means that this parameter will not be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C: Consequence. Value from 0 - 5. 0 means that this parameter will not be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;type-of-category-to-search-by&#34;&gt;Type of category to search by&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the parameters in this section are used for the messages attached to the actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This section is used to search for category groups and categories. Check one or more category groups and / or select categories from the menus. The defining category groups appear at the top. Among them you can only search for one category group and / or category. If a message type or a message form is selected, only the category groups and the categories used in these message forms will appear in this section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;order-by&#34;&gt;Order by&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select the column by which the result table will be sorted.
Show results in&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Table: Show the results in the table of the Search results page for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanded view: Show the results in the expanded view that contains all the action details (previously &amp;ldquo;Printer friendly&amp;rdquo; version) of the Search results page for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graph: Show the result as a chart under Reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Action search results</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/action_search_results/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/action_search_results/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page displays the results when performing an action search and when someone has clicked on an action graph under Reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;search-criteria&#34;&gt;Search criteria&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Displays all the parameters that are used for the search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The drop-down menu for the departments can be used to change the departments from which the actions will be retrieved from. The Navigator can be used to change the department or the department and its subordinate departments from which the actions will be retrieved, depending on what you have selected in the drop-down menu for departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The New search button clears all the search parameters except from the department which is selected in the Navigator and opens the search page for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Expand search button opens the search page for actions with all the parameters listed above in the search criteria list set. You should use this button if you want to continue working with the current search.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graphs: 2 drop-down menus that can be used to change the content or focus of the search and display the result under Reports.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reports: Used to select the graph report type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category groups: The graph depends on the selected graph report type. When Per department / Per category and Per category / category group are selected, the graph shows an overview of the categories that belong to the selected category group. For the other graph report types, only actions with attached messages with checked categories of the selected category group are included in the graph.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search: This button opens the Reports with the parameters set in this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use of the table is explained in Actions.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Actions</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/actions/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Shows all the actions registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator with the status that is selected in one of the underlying tabs. If the underlying tabs have one action for every status, an additional tab for search appears. When performing a search from Action search, the selected search criteria are shown in a separate table above the results table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By clicking on a line in the main table, the action will open in the Action process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about an action, including its history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Expanded view / 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Table.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Table: Toggle between table and expanded view. The table gives a compact description of the actions intended for use when working with them. The expanded view gives a more complete description of the whole action, similar to the printer friendly (.pdf) version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/LeftArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Change page: The arrows are used to change the page when there are more than 20 cases that can be displayed in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Sorting: The table is sorted by the column with the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to sort by another column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_save.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save as file: Allows you to download and save the page as an HTML file on your machine locally. The file can be edited in any application that can edit HTML, including Word.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports, from which you can create a report with the related actions. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tabs here are used for choosing which status you wish to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under planning: Actions that have not been initiated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under execution: Actions that have been assigned to a person responsible for executing them and have been initiated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under approval: Executed actions that are pending approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approved actions: Approved actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search: Advanced search for actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Actions tab worker</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/inbox/tabs/actions_tab_worker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/inbox/tabs/actions_tab_worker/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Used to execute and follow up actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;active-table&#34;&gt;Active Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;By clicking on a row in the main table the action opens.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about an action, including its history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions I need to complete: Displays the non-executed actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions for approval: Displays an overview of the performed actions that are pending approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approved actions: Displays an overview of the performed actions that have been approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Activity</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/activity/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;An activity without an attached list gets no graph, but can still be used to measure participation for example in a meeting or similar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity group: Under which activity group this activity will be placed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity name: The name used to identify the activity wherever it is used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached list: The list attached to this activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From: The date and time when the activity starts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To: The date and time when the activity ends. Note: A day begins at 00:00 and ends at 23:59.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: An activity can be active in multiple languages simultaneously. You must write a name for each language you wish it to have.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The subordinate departments will do the activity: Check this box if the subdepartments of the selected department will participate in the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How often will the activity be performed?: One time is usually selected. Repeating is used if the activity is to be filled out an unlimited number of times by each participant. Periodic is used if the activity will be performed in fixed periods, for example weekly. For the periodic activities the From and To fields must include the entire period, e.g. the whole year if you want to plan weekly activities for a whole year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you want an email reminder before the activity is due?: Sends an email to the person who created the activity at a certain number of days before it ends. The email contains the expected participation and a link to the Follow up page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This activity is answered anonymously: Checkbox that makes the activity anonymous. Comments on anonymous activities will be anonymous.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Number of answers before the result is viewable: Appears only when the anonymity box is checked. The number given here controls how many answers a single department must have before a graph is shown for this department. If too few answers have been given, the sum graph for the department above this in the hierarchy must be used to get a result.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display as list / Display as series of single questions (reminder link only) / Display as control list: Determines the display type of the list. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon to see how the selected list looks like in this display type. Only survey forms should use the option &amp;ldquo;Display as series of single questions&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;Reminder link only&amp;rdquo; means that this display type will only be used when the person who will answer the list has come to it by clicking on the link in the email that is sent out as a reminder for the activity. In the control list display view, there is one checkbox per day per question and the alternative answers do not appear at all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity distribution: Normal or Audit. &amp;ldquo;Audit&amp;rdquo; allows the activity to be answered once for each department the participants have access to. Used as a rule, if you go an inspection round or audit that will be performed by the same user in several places. This option is not included in the standard version. If you want this option enabled, contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:drift@qmplus.com&#34;&gt;drift@qmplus.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roles that will perform the activity: When you associate roles to an activity, only users that have at least one of these roles can participate in it. Only these will be included in the activity&amp;rsquo;s participation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add documents to the activity: Documents attached to the activity will be shown at the top of the list below the heading.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;access-control&#34;&gt;Access control&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;the-different-access-types-give-these-privileges&#34;&gt;The different access types give these privileges&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read access&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can read the contents of a filled out activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Write access&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can fill out or modify the contents of a filled out activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;requirements-for-the-different-access-types&#34;&gt;Requirements for the different access types&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employees have read access to all their own activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managers, case handlers and reviewers have read access to all the activities within their remit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write access
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employees and reviewers have write access to all their own activities within the period they can be filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managers and case handlers have write access to all the activities within their remit and within the period they can be filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Super users with the system role Content administrator have write access to all the activities within their remit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Activity groups</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/tabs/activity_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/tabs/activity_group/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The Activity groups page is used for managing activity groups. It is important that there is at least one activity group, otherwise it will not be possible to create new activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name of the activity group: The name of the activity group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment: A comment about the activity group. Appears only on this screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: Appears only when you have pressed 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Layout_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New activity group or 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit activity group. The text fields of an activity group can be registered in any language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit this activity group: Opens the data fields for the activity group so that they can be changed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Layout_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete activity group: Appears only for activity groups without activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Layout_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New activity group: Opens the data fields to create a new activity group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the data fields of the selected activity group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes the data fields for the requested activity group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Activity plan</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/main/tabs/activity_plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/main/tabs/activity_plan/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Calendar.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 The Activity plan is used for planning and following up activities. Follow up is preselected the first time you open this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Annual plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fill out and results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User participation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Calendar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity groups&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Activity report tab worker</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/tabs/activity_report_tab_worker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/tabs/activity_report_tab_worker/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Displays an overview of all the activities the user has participated in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity group: Restricts the activities in the Activity drop-down menu to the activities from the selected activity group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity: The answers that the user has provided for the selected activity will be shown in the table below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show list: Shows the list associated with the selected activity in list version, as it looks like with the user&amp;rsquo;s answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Prints the current page to .pdf.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes this screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Displays a table for each topic in the list that has been answered. The topic name appears above each table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tables&#34;&gt;Tables&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;summing-up-of-the-answered-list&#34;&gt;Summing up of the answered list&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Question: The question from the list that has been answered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My answers (worker interface) / Answer (manager interface): The answer to the question. For survey forms the text of the selected alternative answer is displayed. For checklists, a checked checkbox is displayed. If the user has commented on his / hers response to a given question, the comment will show here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions I participate in (worker interface) / Actions this user participates in (manager interface): If an action for this question has been created and the user is one of those who will execute it, a link to that action will appear here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other actions (worker interface) / Available actions (manager interface): If an action for this question has been created and the user is not one of those who will execute it, a link to that action will appear here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;all-actions-created-for-the-selected-activity&#34;&gt;All actions created for the selected activity&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This table appears only in the manager interface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Question: The question from the list to which the action is connected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action number: A unique identifier for the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action name: The name of the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department: The department on which the action is registered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: The status of the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Admin</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/main/tabs/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/main/tabs/admin/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Admin is used for managing the system. The access is controlled by the system role Admin. In the standard version, all the managers have full access to edit all information within their own organisation. For some customers this option is limited and therefore they will not get all the tabs that are described below. Contact your local super user if you feel that you need additional rights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All information displayed / posted via Admin will relate to the selected department in the Navigator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode-s0-hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a Super user, I have access to the ADMIN-tab. This tab opens new tabs where I can make changes in the organisation (navigator), add users in the departments, change the categories that will be inserted in message forms, create forms, add new managing documents, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A click on each of the tabs under ADMIN provides access to new tabs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Chart_organisation.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/User.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Users&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Categories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Roles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Wrench.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Rules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/User_suit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Alternative groups</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/tabs/alternative_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/tabs/alternative_groups/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here you can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s alternative groups and alternative groups overviews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;functions&#34;&gt;Functions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selection of alternative groups overviews. The alternative groups that belong to the selected overview are displayed in the table below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New alternative groups overview: Takes you to the New alternative groups overview page to create a new alternative groups overview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit alternative groups overview: Takes you to the Edit alternative groups overview page to edit the selected alternative groups overview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Key_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New alternative group: Creates a new alternative group and takes you to the Edit alternative group page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Copy.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Copies the selected alternative group so that you can continue working with the group that is in use. This icon comes up only if this alternative group is used in a survey form that has already been answered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Endre.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Takes you to the Edit alternative group screen to change the selected alternative group. This icon comes up only if this alternative group is not used in an survey form that has already been answered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Activates / Deactivates the alternative group depending on whether you are under the Deactivated alternative groups tab or the Active alternative groups tab respectively. Deactivated alternative groups can not be selected in the Edit alternative answers screen, but do not affect the list that is in use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Key_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Deletes the selected alternative group. This icon only comes up if this alternative group is not used in a survey form that has already been answered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active lists: Shows the active survey forms available in the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated lists: Shows the deactivated survey forms available in the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active alternative groups: Shows the active alternative groups in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated alternative groups: Shows the deactivated alternative groups in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Annual plan</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/tabs/annual_plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/tabs/annual_plan/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Year: Here you can select a year in order to see the list of all complete and incomplete activities that took place at the selected year.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity group:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show all activities. All activities are shown in the table, regardless of the activity group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List of all activity groups. If you select an activity group, only the activities of the selected activity group are shown in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selection of departments:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To be filled out on this department: Only activities that are to be filled out on the department which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created on subordinate departments: Only activities that were created on the subordinate departments of the one which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created on this and subordinate departments: All activities that were created on the department which is selected in the Navigator and on its subordinate departments are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;headings-in-the-activity-table&#34;&gt;Headings in the activity table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Title: The name of the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reference:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Period: The timeframe for the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: The department from which this activity will be answered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roles that will perform the activity: Roles attached to this activity (if any).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: For common activities, it shows the number of users who answered / the number of users who will participate in the activity. For repetitive activities, it shows the number of users who answered / number users who can participate / the total number of answers. The participation in the activity is also shown in a small bar chart. Completed activities are marked with &amp;ldquo;(Finished)&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comments: The number of comments to the activity. 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Opens the page Comments to the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit: Lists all available-icons for each activity, see below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit this activity: Opens the page Edit activity. For periodic activities, it opens the page Edit date when you are in one of the periods that appear when you have clicked on the RightArrow.gif icon in the Due date column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show printer friendly version: Appears only for activities that have a list attached to them. Opens the preview window to see how the list looks like in the Printer friendly version. In this window you can also choose to see the list in List form and in Single question view, as it will look when it is filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Chart_bar.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 View graph for the results of the checklist: Opens the Graphs for the list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Date_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit date: Shows only for periodic activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Email_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Send reminder for (activity name): Opens the page Send reminder in a separate window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete this activity: Deletes the selected activity. This icon is visible only if:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the selected department in the Navigator is the same as the department from which the activity was created, and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;this activity has not been answered (for periodic activities there must not be any answers in any of the dates), and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the activity has not been completed (its end date has not passed).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New activity: Opens the New activity page to create a new activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Prints the current page to .pdf.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Archive</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/main/tabs/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/main/tabs/archive/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Book.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 The Archive contains all cases in the system. Used for retrieving reports over which cases are being processed, on which department, what is their status. The Search functionality here is used to provide detailed reports over cases selected based on certain criteria and produces the same results as if you were under Reports and clicked on the part of the chart that represents the same criteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All messages: If you select a message form, only cases originating from such a message form will be displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you click on a line of the main table, the selected case will open in its process page. Messages open the Message process page, while actions open the Action process page. Log messages open in the Edit message page, since these are not normally processed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about a case, including its history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configure category columns: Does not show for Actions. Used to select which category group columns will be shown in the table.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The page is reloaded after each change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection affects all tabs in Archive for messages: Messages/NC, Log, Comments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection lasts until you log out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection also affects export to .pdf in Overview table format (&amp;ldquo;Show summary report&amp;rdquo; option in Option page for reports). Only the first 10 category groups will be included in the .pdf.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configure columns: Does not show for Actions. Used to select which columns will be shown in the table.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The page is reloaded after each change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection affects all tabs in Archive for messages: Messages/NC, Log, Comments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection lasts until you log out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection also affects export to .pdf in Overview table format (&amp;ldquo;Show summary report&amp;rdquo; option in Option page for reports).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select messages for export / Cancel selection: Does not show for Actions and is visible only when in Table view. Adds a selection column on the right side of the table, where the user can select which messages will be included in the pdf report. Pagination is lost temporarily and all messages appear in the page. When the Cancel selection is pressed, the Table view and the pagination get restored to their default state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Expanded view / 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Table.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Table: Switch between the expanded and the table view. The table gives a compact description of cases intended for use when working with them. The expanded view gives a more complete description of the whole case, similar to the printer friendly (.pdf) version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports, from which you can create a report with the related cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_save.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save as file: Allows you to download and save the page as an HTML file on your machine locally. The file can be edited in any application that can edit HTML, including Word. Shows only for Actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/LeftArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Change page: The arrows are used to change pages when there are more than 20 cases that can be shown in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Sorting: The table is sorted by the column with the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to sort by another column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages/NC: Registration and overview of messages that follow the usual handling process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Log: Registration and overview of log messages. Not included in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comments: Overview of comment messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions: Overview of actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Attached messages</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/attached_messages/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/action/tabs/attached_messages/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Several messages can be attached to or detached from the action. Approved actions can not be attached to several messages or detached from messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;messages-attached-to-this-action&#34;&gt;Messages attached to this action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A table showing messages attached to this action. There must always be at least one message connected to an action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about a message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the Show message icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_magnify.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 in the last column in order to look at or edit a message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the Detach message icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to detach the selected message from the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;messages-that-are-not-closed&#34;&gt;Messages that are not closed&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A table showing the open messages that are not attached to this action. Above the table are some search options, so that not all the open messages are shown at the same time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select a category group: Here you can select criteria so that the messages shown in the table below will be similar to the ones that are already attached to this action.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Defining category: The message must have have the same defining category checked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;Category group name&gt;: The message must have the same category of the selected category group checked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Any category: The message must have the same category checked in at least one category group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity: The message must be a comment message to the same activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List element: The message must be a comment message to the same question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show messages from this and subordinate departments
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Yes: Messages from this and the subordinate departments will be included in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No: Only messages from this department will be included in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search: Click on this when you have made the selection in the fields above to update the table below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about a message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the Show message icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_magnify.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 in the last column in order to look at or edit a message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the Attach message icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to attach the selected message to the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;delete-action&#34;&gt;Delete action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Button that appears only for users with the system role content administrator. Detaches all messages from this action and deletes the action. Messages attached to other open actions get the status Action process. Messages only attached to other closed actions get the status Closed. Messages not attached to other actions get the status New.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action process: Opens the Action process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached messages: Reloads this screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Audit</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/audit/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;In Qm+, the term audit means control of the quality system and is used for the process of reviewing and approving one or more documents. This applies both to reviewing the document content and the status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example: You read the document that describes a routine. Does the routine correspond to reality?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If yes, then the document has been revised.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If no, then you have to either change the practice of the company, or the document&amp;rsquo;s content must be rewritten so that the description corresponds to reality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is important to check if the document has newer versions than the one which is published. In that case, this will show in the list of documents that are associated with the audit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode-s0-hbhb-what-can-i-do-in-this-page&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do in this page?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set start date and due date for the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select the documents that will be included in this audit. Use the button Add documents to audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click Save to create the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audited and Remove appear for every document that is added to the table.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check Audited after you have read / controlled and possibly changed something in the document contents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check Remove if you want to remove the document from this audit (table) or if you regret auditing this document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When all the documents have Audited checked, and you click Save, then the button Complete the audit appears. Click on it and the audit is completed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Description&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents can have a warning date for the audit. The warning is sent to an audit responsible. The notified user or a manager / case handler on the same department or on a department above it can then create an audit or add the document to an existing audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active documents can be freely added to audits even if they do not have an audit warning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A document can only be associated with one open audit at a time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An audit does not have its own hearings associated with it, but the page where you can edit an audit shows information about any hearings that the documents associated with this audit are part of.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To create a new hearing for a document that is part of an audit you have to open the Hearing / Approval tab in the Edit document data page. A saved audit shows direct links to the Edit document data page for each associated document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each audit for which the start date has passed is shown as a row in the Inbox / My current cases for the user who must perform the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An audit is regarded as open until it is completed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To complete an audit, all associated documents must be approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A completed audit can not be changed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit creator. The user who created and will perform the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department. The department where the audit was created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start date. The date when the audit starts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due date. The due date for the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completed. The date when the audit was completed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information. Free text. Additional information for this audit. Use as needed. The content is displayed in the tables that show the audits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents. An audit can have an unlimited number of documents associated with it. The audit date and the name of the user who did the audit for each document appear after a document has been approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Audit overview</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/audit_overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/audit_overview/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Shows a table with all the audits that the document has been through. Click on a row in the table to open the actual audit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit number. Identifier for the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information. Free text field with information entered by the audit responsible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit responsible. The name of the user who is responsible for doing the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department. The name of the department where the audit was created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start date. The date when the audit starts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due date. The due date for the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completed. The date when the audit was completed. Otherwise blank.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Calendar</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/tabs/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/tabs/calendar/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The Calendar screen shows an annual time chart of when the activities of the company should be executed. The activities are ordered by activity group and the time is given in week numbers. The current week number is marked with bold numbers. If an activity is active for at least one day in a given week, this week will be marked in the time chart. Activities that have not started are shown in blue, activities in progress are shown in orange, and finished ones are shown in green.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;headings-in-the-table&#34;&gt;Headings in the table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity name: The name of the activities that are active in the selected period. The blue activity names can be clicked on and open the Fill out and results for the selected activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time period: The selected time period. Use 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/ArrowclosedLeft.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to change the time period (year).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Show as pdf: Prints the current page to .pdf (without the colours).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Print: Prints the current page. The option Print background colours and images must be checked in your web browser, located under the Advanced menu in Internet Options for Internet Explorer, so that the time table is printed correctly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Cases I am responsible for</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/inbox/tabs/cases_i_am_responsible_for/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/inbox/tabs/cases_i_am_responsible_for/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Cases I am responsible for shows cases that the logged in user has to work with, regardless of the department which is selected in the Navigator. This tab is not shown if the user can not process messages, perform actions, participate in hearings or perform document audits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pink cases are messages, yellow cases are actions, blue-gray cases are hearings. Audit warnings have no colour.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;options&#34;&gt;Options&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Register new message: Select a message form to register a new message. Opens the Edit message page. The message forms are displayed as individual buttons if there are up to 4 different forms. If there are more, the button 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Register new message must be pressed first. This opens a list of all active message forms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All cases drop-down menu: If you select a message form, only cases originating from such a form are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cases I am responsible for / All cases I have been involved in: When &amp;ldquo;Cases I am responsible for&amp;rdquo; is selected, only cases that the logged in user should do something about are shown. When &amp;ldquo;All cases I have been involved in&amp;rdquo; is selected, the list shown below includes also the cases that the logged in user has done something about but they are not closed yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/LeftArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Change page: The arrows are used to change the page when there are more than 20 cases that can be displayed in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Sort_down.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/No_sort.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Sorting: The table is sorted by the column with the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Sort_down.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


. Click on 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/No_sort.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to sort on another column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_green.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


,

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_yellow.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


,

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_red.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Priority: Symbolize low, medium and high priority respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;main-table&#34;&gt;Main table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you click on a line of the main table, the selected case will open in its handling page. Messages open in the Message process page, actions open in the Action process page and hearings open in the Reply to a hearing page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+ Extra Information and History: Hold the cursor over the + symbol to get more information about the case. Currently, only for messages and actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message form: Which message form was used to create the case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered: The date when the case was registered. For messages when they were registered, for actions when they were created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due: For messages this is the handling deadline, for actions this is the execution and approval deadline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Description: For messages this is the text in the first text field of the message, for actions this is their name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_green.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


,

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_yellow.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


,

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_red.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 symbolize low, medium and high priority respectively. For actions, this is the priority of the attached message to them with the highest priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: The status of the case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered on department: The department where the case was originally registered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current case handler: The name of the user who is responsible for handling the case. Depends on the type and status of the case. Shows only when the option &amp;ldquo;All cases I have been involved in&amp;rdquo; is selected above the table.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;The name of a user&gt;: This user is the assigned responsible person for the case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;Under planning&amp;raquo;: The name of the user who has created the action and is responsible for it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;Under execution&amp;raquo;: The names of the users who will execute the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;Under approval&amp;raquo;: The name of the user who has created the action and is responsible for approving it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;On hearing&amp;raquo;: The names of the users who will participate in the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;For approval&amp;raquo;: The name of the user who will approve the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;which-cases-are-shown-in-the-table&#34;&gt;Which cases are shown in the table?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages sent to the logged in user via Send to case handler under Message process or via the Early case process under Edit message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For managers (users with the system role default message receiver):
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages registered on the department where the manager is registered on and have not been assigned to another responsible person.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages registered on a subordinate department where there isn&amp;rsquo;t a manager, and have not been assigned to another responsible person. Messages registered on departments without a manager will be moved upwards in the organisation hierarchy and will appears in the Inbox on the first department above that has a manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions that the user has created and are being planned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions that the user has to execute and are under execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions that the user is assigned as action approver for. This assignment is done either by creating the action or by a rule of type action approver.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearings that the user has to participate in and are on hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearings that the user has to approve and are under approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit warning for documents that have passed their audit warning date and the user is set as audit responsible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audits the user has to do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that messages other users have registered which were made with message forms that have a role with the &amp;ldquo;See messages&amp;rdquo; limitation, will not be shown here unless the logged in user has the same role or the system role See all messages attached to him / her or to the user type the user is logged in with. Messages which the user himself / herself has registered will be shown.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Categories</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/admin/tabs/categories/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/admin/tabs/categories/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Here you can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s categories and category groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode-s1-hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ADMIN-tab gives me the possibility to make changes in Categories. (These can later be added to the message form: Click Forms.)
Here you can create a new Category group. Click on the tab &amp;ldquo;Active category groups&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next page gives you the possibility to select if the group will be multi choice, single choice (radio button), number or defining category.
If you select the tab &amp;ldquo;Active categories&amp;rdquo; you can select between the category groups in the drop-down menu on the left above the table. Then click on the &amp;ldquo;New category&amp;rdquo; button.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category group selection: Lists all active category groups in the system. All categories in the selected group created from the selected department in the Navigator will be shown in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New category: Creates a new category and takes you to the Edit category screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Takes you to the Edit category page to change the selected category.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Activates / Deactivates the selected category, depending on whether you are under the tab Deactivated categories or Active categories respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete: Deletes the selected category. Visible only under the Deactivated categories for categories that are not in use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active categories: Displays the active categories created in the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated categories: Displays the deactivated categories created in the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active category groups: Displays the active category groups which are accessible from the department that is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated category groups: Displays the disabled category groups which are accessible from the department that is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Categories submenu message form</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/forms/tabs/categories_submenu_message_form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/forms/tabs/categories_submenu_message_form/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here you can manage the categories of the message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;add-categories-to-the-message-form&#34;&gt;Add categories to the message form&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this panel you can manage the categories of the message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The left panel shows the categories that are already in the message form, the right panel shows the categories that can be added. The panels are filtered by the category group which is selected in the category group drop-down menu above the left panel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a category in the left panel is marked with yellow, it will appear both when the message form is opened at the department where the category was added and at any subordinate department. Categories in white are only shown when opening the form at the same department where the category was added. This is set by the state of the &amp;ldquo;Show for subdepartments&amp;rdquo; checkbox (checked or not) when adding a category to the message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entries marked with &amp;ldquo;Advanced option&amp;rdquo; are only shown when the Show advanced options button in the Edit message form page has been clicked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose category group: The fields below this drop-down menu will only contain categories belonging to the selected category group. The category groups in this drop-down menu are grouped by category group type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Order type (Advanced option): Shown above the category group drop-down menu at the panel Add categories to the message form.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ordering by Type is the default and means that the category groups will be sorted by their category group type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ordering by Index means that you can assign a column (left, center or right) and an index to each category group in the message form. If the sorting is to be done by index, one should go through all the category groups and set the column and index. The Save button must be pressed after each change so that it will be put into effect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show as: Determines how the selected category group will appear in the message form (Checkbox / Drop-down menu).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that a category group needs to have either some of its own categories or some categories of a sub group attached to the message form for the following options to have any effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display in the message form (Advanced option): Determines if and how the given category group should appear in the message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display in the message process page (Advanced option): Determines if and how the given category group should appear in the message process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display in the action process page (Advanced option): Determines if and how the given category group should appear in the action process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display in Inbox (Advanced option): If set to Yes, then an extra column will appear under Inbox, where the checked categories that belong to this category group will be listed for messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display in the mobile app (Advanced option): If set to No, this category group will not appear in the message form when displayed in the mobile application. This field is visible only if the mobile application is activated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mandatory: If set to Yes, the user will have to select a category in this group in order for a message created with this message form to be saved. Defining category groups are a special case and will always have Yes here. Note that if a message form has more than one defining category groups, the mandatory requirement will work so that only one of the categories in all the defining category groups will have to be checked before a message can be saved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


New category: Opens the New category screen with the Category group set to the same category group as the one selected in the drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


&amp;laquo; Add: Adds the selected categories in the right panel to this message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Remove &amp;raquo;: Removes the selected categories in the left panel from this message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_go.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Edit category dependency for the selected category. Opens the page Edit category dependency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;categories-in-this-message-form&#34;&gt;Categories in this message form&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Displays a table for each category group with the categories associated with the message form. The table shows the name of the category and the department it was attached from. To delete a category from a message form, one must have selected the same department in the Navigator as the department where the category was attached from.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Category groups</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/admin/tabs/category_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/admin/tabs/category_groups/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here you can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s category groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Package_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New category group: Creates a new category group and takes you to the Edit category group page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Takes you to the Edit category group page to change the category group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Activate / Deactivate the category group, depending on whether you are under Deactivated category groups or Active category groups respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Checklists</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/tabs/checklists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/tabs/checklists/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here you can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s checklists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selection of list types: Select the list type you wish to see an overview for. The list type is only a way to organise lists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


New list: Creates a new checklist and takes you to the New list screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_gear.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Takes you to the Edit list information screen to edit the information on the selected checklist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Takes you to the Edit list content screen to edit the questions of the selected checklist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Opens the preview window to see how the list looks in the printer friendly version. In this window you can also choose to see the list in list form or as a series of single questions which is how it will look when it will be filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Activates / Deactivates the list depending on whether you are under the tab Deactivated lists or Active lists respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_copy.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Copy list: Creates a copy of the selected checklist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Deletes the selected list. This icon appears only if the tab Deactivated lists is selected and if the checklist has not been used in an activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_save.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Opens the page Export to the common library. If this icon is disabled / grayed out, the list is already in the common library.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active lists: Shows the active lists that are available in the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated lists: Shows the deactivated lists that are available in the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Common library: Opens the common library for checklists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Comment reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/comment_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/comment_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The graphs for the comment messages are shown here.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Comments</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/archive/tabs/comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/archive/tabs/comments/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Contains all the comment messages in the system. Comment messages are messages that are registered when filling out a list distributed through the Activity plan. When performing a search either from Reports or from the Message search, the selected search criteria are shown in a separate table above the results table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;selections&#34;&gt;Selections&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All messages drop-down menu: Select a message form and only messages originating from that message form will be shown. Only message forms of the type Log are shown here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Calendar.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Date search: From date, To date. Only messages registered in the period displayed here are shown in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you click on a line of the main table, the selected message will open in the Message process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about a message, including its history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Find.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Search: Update the table of messages based on the selected dates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configure category columns: Used to select which category group columns will be shown in the table.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The page is reloaded after each change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection affects all tabs in Archive for messages: Messages/NC, Log, Comments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection lasts until you log out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection also affects export to .pdf in Overview table format (&amp;ldquo;Show summary report&amp;rdquo; option in Option page for reports). Only the first 10 category groups will be included in the .pdf.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Configure columns: Used to select which columns will be shown in the table.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The page is reloaded after each change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection affects all tabs in Archive for messages: Messages/NC, Log, Comments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection lasts until you log out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The column selection also affects export to .pdf in Overview table format (&amp;ldquo;Show summary report&amp;rdquo; option in Option page for reports).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select messages for export / Cancel selection: Visible only when in Table view. Adds a selection column on the right side of the table, where the user can select which comment messages will be included in the pdf report. Pagination is lost temporarily and all comments appear in the page. When the Cancel selection is pressed, the Table view and the pagination get restored to their default state.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Expanded view / 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Table.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Table: Switch between the expanded and the table view. The table gives a compact description of comment messages intended for use when working with them. The expanded view gives a more complete description of the whole comment message, similar to the printer friendly (.pdf) version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports, from which you can create a report with the related comment messages. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/LeftArrow.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Change page: The arrows are used to change pages when there are more than 20 cases that can be shown in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Sorting: The table is sorted by the column with the - 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to sort by another column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Log overview: All the comment messages that are registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Search: Opens the Message search with the form type Comment preselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Comments to the activity</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/functions/comments_to_the_activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/functions/comments_to_the_activity/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Used for viewing all the comment messages, actions and reports for an activity or a question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;headings&#34;&gt;Headings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The headline says for which activity or activities are the data shown in the table below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The smaller heading &amp;ldquo;Concerning question&amp;rdquo; below says for which question in the list are the data shown in the table below. If this heading is not here, the data for the whole list is displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show comments / actions: Document type selection.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show comments: Comment messages are shown in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show actions: Actions are shown in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show reports: Activity reports are shown in the table. Not included in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action location selection: Appears only when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions registered on: Takes into account only the department on which the action is registered. This is the department that the user had selected in the Navigator when &amp;ldquo;Create new action&amp;rdquo; was pressed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions with executors from: Takes into account only the department on which those that are set up to perform the action are registered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department selection: Appears only when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This department: Only cases that belong to the department which is selected in the Navigator appear in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This and subordinate departments: Cases that belong to the department which is selected in the Navigator or to its subordinate departments appear in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports, from which you can create a report with the related comment messages. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Expanded view / 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Table.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Table: Switch between the expanded and the table view. The table gives a compact description of the comment messages intended for use when working with them. The expanded view gives a more complete description of the comment messages, similar to the printer friendly (.pdf) version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the active window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Report.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Report: Create a new report for this activity. Not included in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create new action: Creates a new action for the element in the list that is described by the headlines.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If &amp;ldquo;Show comments&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu, all selected comments in the table below will be attached to the new action. All comments are preselected. Click on the checkbox on the column header (next to &amp;ldquo;Select&amp;rdquo;) to select or deselect all comments at the same time or click on specific comments to (de)select them one at a time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu, the new action will be blank and will be attached to a &amp;ldquo;dummy&amp;rdquo; message which will not be editable and will not be used otherwise. You can use this when you need to create an action for a question to which no comments were added.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The button does not appear when &amp;ldquo;Show reports&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Sends you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Sort on this column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: The table is sorted on this column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/LeftArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: If there are several pages, scroll forward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: If there are several pages, scroll backward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;+: Hold the cursor over this field to get extended information about the case, including its history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered: When was the case registered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due: The deadline for the case. Does not appear when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Question: The question for which the comment was written. Does not appear when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment: Text written from the user as a comment to this question. Does not appear when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: Does not appear when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: The status of the action or comment message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operative department: The department by which the comment is being processed. Does not appear when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu. Does not show for anonymous activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select: When you press the &amp;ldquo;Create new action&amp;rdquo; button, the state of the checkbox determines if the new action will be attached to the current comment (selected) or not (not selected). Appears only when &amp;ldquo;Show comments&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action name: Appears only when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executor: Who will execute the action. Appears only when &amp;ldquo;Show actions&amp;rdquo; is selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Common library</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/tabs/common_library/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/tabs/common_library/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here you can see all the forms that have been added to the common library of the customers of Qm+, for the form type you are under. Used for exchanging forms. Documents are planned for a later version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form type. All forms that are uploaded to the common library can be marked with various keywords. Use this drop-down menu to see only those forms that are tagged with the selected keyword.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Opens the preview window to see how the list looks in the printer friendly version. In this window you can also choose to see the list in list version and in single question view as it will look when it will be filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_go.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Imports the current form into your Qm+ database. Please note that for message forms, all the category groups and categories in the form that do not already exist in your database will be created on the department you are when you click on this icon. This icon can be deactivated / grayed out. This means that the form already exists in your database.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Deletes the current form. This icon appears only to the user who uploaded the form in the common library.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Definitions</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/other/definitions_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/other/definitions_2/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h1 id=&#34;alternative-group&#34;&gt;Alternative group&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A collection of alternative answers that can be connected to questions in a survey form. Managed in the alternative groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An alternative group belongs to a specific alternative groups overview. This is used only to distinguish between alternative groups under Edit alternative answers and under Alternative groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;category-group&#34;&gt;Category group&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A category group is used for grouping categories within the same topic and for setting properties for categories. In a message form, a category group is displayed as a headline over its corresponding categories. How it is displayed and how it works depends on the category group type. Each category group that is created, creates automatically a new report under Reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Category groups can also be used to identify groups of specific messages and actions via the search page for messages and the search page for actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managed under Edit category group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: The name of a category group can be set once for every language that is activated in the system. Appears only for customers who have multiple active languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category group type: The type of the category group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category group name: The name used to represent the category group. A category group can have one name for each active language in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: From which level in the hierarchy the category group will be available.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information: Text that appears when you hold the cursor over the category group name in a message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;advanced-options&#34;&gt;Advanced options&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Class: Default or Tasks. Categories of groups that are classified as Tasks represent a department&amp;rsquo;s main tasks and are shown in the Edit department page. This will later be expanded with positions and competence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subgroup of: If the category group is a subgroup of another category group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shown for subdepartments?: Yes / No. If the category group will be visible also to all the subordinate departments of the selected department or only for the selected department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;defining-category&#34;&gt;Defining category&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A defining category is the category that describes what a message is about. It is mandatory to select a defining category for a message form to be saved. A defining category is defined by the fact that it belongs to a category group with a defined category group type. On a message form, defining categories are marked with the icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tag_blue.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and you can only select one of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;display-type&#34;&gt;Display type&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Controls how the list is displayed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Possible display types: Printer friendly, List version (or List form), Single question view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;document-group&#34;&gt;Document group&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A document group is a grouping of documents used to control which group of documents will appear under Info. Each document group is shown in a coloured box with the document group&amp;rsquo;s name as the heading. A document group must contain at least one document belonging to the selected document tab for it to appear under the relative tab under Info. If a document group has documents that belong to various document tabs, then the document group will appear in each of these document tabs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managed under Edit document group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Documents can be assigned to document groups under Edit document data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: The name of a document group can be registered once for every language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: Used to identify the document group in tables and overviews. A document group can have one name for each language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position: The position of the document group under Info. In the standard version two document groups are displayed side by side. The next two will appear below these again until all the document groups are displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: The document group will appear under Info from the selected department and from its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shown for subdepartments: If no, the document group will only appear under Info when the department selected under &amp;ldquo;From department&amp;rdquo; is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Background colour: If you want a special background colour for the document group, you can select it here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;hearing&#34;&gt;Hearing&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hearing is used when a group of users should be able to comment on the contents of a document. The hearing is connected to a version of a document, so that there can be several hearing rounds on the same document.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hearing goes through the following phases:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;On hearing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For approval&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approved&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hearing is created under Edit document data, under the tab Hearing / Approval. It can be answered under Reply to a hearing that appears under Info, when opening the received hearing notification. A user receives a notification that (s)he has to participate in a hearing or that (s)he has to approve it under Cases I am responsible for and possibly by e-mail.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;log-reports&#34;&gt;Log reports&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Log is a tab under Reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The graphs for the log messages are shown here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This tab appears only if the log messages are enabled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;manager&#34;&gt;Manager&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the preconfigured user types in the system delivered with the standard version. Name and roles for all user types may be altered by the System administrator. The capabilities of the user type are defined by the system roles assigned to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;message-status&#34;&gt;Message status&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messages in Qm+ have a status that represents where they are in the handling process. The status of a message changes under Message process, the status of an action changes under Action process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New: The message is only registered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sent to case handler: The message has been assigned to a responsible person with a deadline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action in progress: Only under Archive. The message is connected to an action that has not yet been approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Closed:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under Reports: The message has been connected to an action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under Archive: The action that the message is connected to has been approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rejected: The message has been rejected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a message is connected to an action or rejected, it will be locked and it will no longer be possible to edit or process it, except from users with the system role content administrator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messages that are handled immediately, will be closed directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;print&#34;&gt;Print&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Opens the print dialog of your browser in order to print the current page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you do not want to print the entire image or the print command does not print the part of the screen you want, try clicking the right button of the mouse in the field you want printed. Then choose Print from the menu that appears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For users with high screen resolution the print out can be larger than the printer paper size. Trick to fix it:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose reduced size for the printing. How this is done varies between different browsers and printers. Look for Scale, Reduce / Enlarge or a percentage (%) field. These can usually be found under the advanced options.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reduce the size of your browser window so that it looks more like the paper in the printer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower the resolution of your screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Copy the part of the page you want to print out and paste it into an external program such as Word or a photo program, and print it from there. You can do this by pressing Prt Scr (Print Screen) on your keyboard and then pasting it by Ctrl + v at the desired application (for Windows PCs).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to save the page as a PDF file instead of printing it on a printer, you can download and install the program PDFCreator. Next time you select Print or press Ctrl + P in your browser, you will be able to select PDFCreator as the printer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;question&#34;&gt;Question&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A list consists of topics and questions. A question may have an extra information field to provide additional information on the question. For survey forms, each question is also associated with an alternative group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Questions are managed from Edit list content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;reference&#34;&gt;Reference&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A reference is a document that is associated with an activity or a list and has also been marked as a reference. References are shown in tables and overviews along with the name of the corresponding activity. Activities inherit the reference affiliation from the list to which they are associated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference functionality is an option that is not included in the standard version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;reviewer&#34;&gt;Reviewer&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reviewer is a user type in the standard version of Qm+ that has the same access rights as the user type manager. That means full access to read all cases within their remit, as well as reports via Reports and Activity plan. Reviewers have no access to Admin. Reviewers can register new messages on their own department and can edit only their own cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;role-group&#34;&gt;Role group&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Role groups are used to sort roles. They are intended to be used by those customers who need to assign many different roles to multiple users. Instead of picking out roles one by one, one can instead simply assign all those roles in a role group for the various users.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All roles belong to one or more role groups. The roles that have not been assigned to a role group belong to no role group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Role groups are managed under Edit role group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;search-criteria&#34;&gt;Search criteria&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Search criteria are the selected options when performing a search. They define what we search for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They are shown in a table above the search results whenever a search is performed. A search may be started from Reports, from Search message, from Search action or by clicking on the risk matrix under Risk. All search results are shown in table form under Archive or as charts under Reports, under their respective tab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All criteria shown in drop-down menus can be changed. Such changes update the search results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Criteria followed by the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon can be removed from the search criteria. This also updates the search results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;single-question-view&#34;&gt;Single question view&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display type for lists. Used primarily for survey forms. Shows one question at a time with its own comment field if it should be possible to comment on the question. The answer is saved only when the Save button at the last question is pressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;subgroup&#34;&gt;Subgroup&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Subgroups are used to create grouped drop-down menus of categories in a message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The name of the category group to which the other groups are subgroups will be the title above the drop-down menu. Any categories in this group will then be listed at the top of the drop-down menu. Under these, there will be a heading in the drop-down menu for each subgroup. All the categories in the subgroup will be listed under this heading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is possible to select only one of the categories in such a drop-down menu.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a special functionality that one can usually discuss with QmPlus AS before using it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;topic&#34;&gt;Topic&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A topic in a list is a headline over a set of questions. A topic can have an extra information field that appears under the heading when the list is answered. All questions in a list must belong to a topic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maintained under Edit list content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;answer-type&#34;&gt;Answer type&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every question in a list can have an answer type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;answer-types&#34;&gt;Answer types:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Single choice: One answer to each question. Even if one answer for a question is already selected, you should still answer the question. This is the default answer which will be used unless a change is made.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple choice: You can select as many alternative answers to each question as you wish, from none to all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Text: There will not be any check boxes for this question, only a comment field. Does not apply to the list version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free text number: A number can be entered in response to this question. The graph will show the sum of all the numbers written as a reply to such a question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tip: Use the answer type Multi choice for questions with only one alternative answer, as in a checklist. Otherwise it will not be possible for users to remove the check mark if they change their mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;case&#34;&gt;Case&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A case in Qm+ is either a message, an action, a hearing or an audit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;category&#34;&gt;Category&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A category is in most cases a checkbox in a message form. All categories belong to a category group. The category group type of the category group determines how the category will appear in the message form. All information that is entered in relation to a category in a message form can be extracted as a report via Reports. The categories can also be used to identify groups of specific messages via the search page for messages and the search page for actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managed under Edit category.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-1&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: The name of a category can be set once for every language that is activated in the system. Appears only for customers who have multiple active languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category group: The category&amp;rsquo;s group. The category group type of the category group determines how this category will look like in a message form. A text at the bottom of this screen describes the type of the selected group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category name: The name used to represent the category. A category can have one name for every language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: Low, Medium, High. The predefined priority of a category. Can be overridden by the person who fills out the message form. The priority of a message is the highest priority of the checked categories unless it is overridden by the user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cost: The predefined cost of a category. Can be overridden by the person who fills out the message form. The cost of a message is the sum of the costs of the checked categories, unless it is overridden by the user. Cost functionality can be removed for those who wish it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: The category is available from the selected department and its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached document: The document that will be activated if you click on the category in the message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information: Text field that is visible when you hold the cursor over the category in the message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Risk data: Appear only for the categories belonging to a category group with the category group type Risk. Used to set different acceptance criteria for various risk categories.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start yellow risk area: Overviews of this category will give a yellow risk value from (and including) this risk value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start red risk area: Overviews of this category will give a red risk value from (and including) this risk value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;category-group-type&#34;&gt;Category group type&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The category group type of a category group determines how the categories in the group will be displayed and answered in a message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;types&#34;&gt;Types&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;defining-category-1&#34;&gt;Defining category&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intended to describe what is the topic of a message. Single choice for the whole message form. If there are several defining groups in a message form, it will only be possible to check one category in one of the groups. A message form can only be saved if a category which belongs to a defining category group is checked. Defining categories are obligatory to fill out in a a message form. Defining categories usually appear at the upper part of the screen to the left with an orange background colour and are marked with the icon Tag blue.png.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;single-choice&#34;&gt;Single choice&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used to provide additional information in a message form. One choice per group. Shown to the left under the defining categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;multi-choice&#34;&gt;Multi Choice&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used to provide additional information in a message form. Any number can be checked. Shown on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;action&#34;&gt;Action&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used to provide detailed information on what kind of action should be used to deal with the conditions that the message is about. Any number can be checked. The categories in this group are taken further in the action, if one is created for a message. Shown in the center below the text fields in the message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;number&#34;&gt;Number&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Provides a text field where any number can be entered. Selecting a group of this type in the Reports would cause the cost graph to be replaced with a graph showing the sum of the values in these fields. Shown to the right in the message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;risk&#34;&gt;Risk&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each category of this type has two drop-down menus, where a value from 1 to 5 can be selected. The first symbolizes the probability that the event will happen, the second symbolizes the consequence. These values are automatically multiplied to produce a risk value. The risk value gets a colour based on limits set for the category. Messages with values &amp;gt; 0 for a risk category will appear in the risk report under Reports. Shown in the center of the message form under the Action categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;comment-form&#34;&gt;Comment form&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A message form that is associated with a question in a list is called a comment form. This message form is used for registering the comments given when replying to a list. If the display type single question view is used, the text above the comment field will be the name of the first text field in the comment form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This link between the list and the message form means that all comments on an activity can be handled and given feedback to as if they were ordinary messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The comment form for a list can be selected under Edit list information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;filling-out&#34;&gt;Filling out&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The function of filling out a list. Its appearance is determined by the list type and the selected display type for the activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See &amp;ldquo;Filling out a list form&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Filling out a list in single question view&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;graph-report-types&#34;&gt;Graph report types&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Graph report types can be selected under Reports, Message search and Action search to determine which kind of reports will be displayed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;graph-report-types-1&#34;&gt;Graph report types&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Per department: Shows one graph per department for the department which is selected in the Navigator and one for each directly subordinate department to that one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Per department / Per category: If all the category groups are selected in the category group drop-down menu, then one graph per category group will be shown. If a particular category group is selected in the category group drop-down menu, then one graph per department for the department which is selected in the Navigator and one for each directly subordinate department to that one will be shown . This graph is colour coded so that each category in the selected category group will be marked with a different colour. This report has one graph for numbers and one for percentages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Per category / category group: If all the category groups are selected in the category group drop-down menu, then one graph per category group is displayed. If a particular category group is selected in the category group drop-down menu, then one graph per each category that belongs to the selected category group is displayed. When there are many reported messages in a category group, then this is the report that provides the best overview.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Status: Provides a graph bar per message status.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Priority: Provides a graph bar per priority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Distribution over time: Provides a graph bar per unit of time. Which unit is chosen depends on the selected time period.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Risk report: Provides a risk matrix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;List: Lists all the categories in the report grouped by category group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;list-type&#34;&gt;List type&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The List type controls how a list will be displayed to the user. The different list types are: Checklists, Risk analysis lists and Survey forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;log-message&#34;&gt;Log message&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Log messages are messages that normally do not need to be handled, just registered and saved in the archive. Examples of such use can be minutes and documentation of legal execution. Log messages do not therefore appear under the Inbox unless you use Message process to activate them. The message type log message is not enabled in the standard version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Log messages are in all other ways identical to the regular messages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;message-type&#34;&gt;Message type&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All messages have a message type. A message gets the same message type as the message form it was registered with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-different-message-types&#34;&gt;The different message types&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message: Common messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Log message: Registered in the Log under Archive. Not included in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Risk message: Registered in the Risk under Archive. Not included in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If neither log messages or risk messages are enabled in your system, the term message type will not be used.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;mobile-version&#34;&gt;Mobile version&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mobile version of Qm+ is a separate interface adapted for display on mobile devices. The customization is done by sending over only the most important information and displays everything as short texts. It is possible to register messages, checklists and survey forms in this version. All information registered is visible in the normal Qm+ version in the same way as everything else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The homepage for the mobile version is wap.qmplus.net. Logging in is done using the same company, username and password as for the normal login.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mobile version is an additional module that must be ordered separately.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;printer-friendly&#34;&gt;Printer friendly&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A printer friendly version is a message form or an action that is adapted in order to print well on paper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;risk-matrix&#34;&gt;Risk matrix&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A risk matrix shows an overview of Probability and Consequence in a 5 x 5 matrix. The fields are coloured green, yellow and red to symbolise the different acceptance levels for the risk value.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Qm+ has a risk matrix under Reports for each message type. The matrix under Message Reports refers to real events, while the matrix under Risk Reports shows an overview of potential incidents. The matrix of potential incidents appears also under Archive / Risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;risk-value&#34;&gt;Risk value&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Risk value (R) is the result of the multiplication of probability (P) and consequence (C).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;P * C = R.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The risk value is often visualised in a risk matrix.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At a risk assessment, one wishes to reduce the risk value. This is done by showing the probability- and consequence-reducing measures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;role-overview&#34;&gt;Role overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Role overview: Used for assigning roles to a document. Opens from Edit document data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A document without roles:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;is available to all users from the department where the document was created and from its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A document with associated roles appears under Info only for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;users assigned to one or more of the same roles.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;users who have chosen a department associated with one or more of the same roles of the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roles do not limit the access to documents under Admin / Documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;standard-version&#34;&gt;Standard version&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The standard version of Qm+ is the one with the system settings that is given to new customers if they do not ask for any changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The customer&amp;rsquo;s contact person with QmPlus AS may order changes from the standard version. Most changes to system settings are done free of charge. Contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:drift@qmplus.com&#34;&gt;drift@qmplus.com&lt;/a&gt; if you have questions or change requests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See system roles for the set up of user types in the standard version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;super-user&#34;&gt;Super user&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The super user is a user who has taken the super user course of Qm+. The super user has the highest access to Qm+ within the company. The super user will assist the other users in the company and will act as local support for Qm+.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All super users are entitled to free telephone support from Qm+ and can take advantage of this if they receive a question from their company users that they need help to answer. As a rule, one or more of the company&amp;rsquo;s super users also function as contact persons between the company and QmPlus AS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All requests for changing some functionality in the system must be communicated via the customer&amp;rsquo;s contact person, so that we know that this is a request of the entire company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;system-role&#34;&gt;System role&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;System roles are roles that are preset in the system and provide specific rights for using Qm+. System roles are defined by QmPlus AS but can be given from certain super users to users or user types. This is advanced functionality and is usually not turned on for new customers at the beginning. Contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:drift@qmplus.com&#34;&gt;drift@qmplus.com&lt;/a&gt; if you need this right or if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can find a list of the available system roles here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;tab&#34;&gt;Tab&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The navigation structure of Qm+ is made up of tabs. They have a name that describes the location of the system you can go to if you click on them. Most also have a descriptive text that appears when you hover the mouse pointer over them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tabs also describe where you are in the system. The tabs that are darker than the others are selected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Example :&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arkfanebeskrivelse.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;



&lt;h1 id=&#34;user&#34;&gt;User&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A user is a set of information that identifies a real person who will be using Qm+.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managed under Admin / Users / Edit user information by users having access to that tab or under Preferences for others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-2&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User name: Used by the user for logging into the system. Distinguishes between uppercase and lowercase letters. Must be unique for each customer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department: The department to which the user belongs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Type: The user&amp;rsquo;s user type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Password: Used by the user for logging into the system. Distinguishes between uppercase and lowercase letters.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeat password: Must be identical with the password field in order for the user&amp;rsquo;s data to be saved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First name: The user&amp;rsquo;s first name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Middle name: The user&amp;rsquo;s middle name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Surname: The user&amp;rsquo;s last name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email address: The user&amp;rsquo;s email address. Some functionality of the system is linked to the user&amp;rsquo;s email address. It is therefore preferred that each user has a unique email address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language: Selection of the display language for the user. Available languages in the system are: Norwegian (bokmål), Norwegian (nynorsk), English, Swedish and Danish (not translated framework for Danish). The available languages for each customer will vary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile number: Can be used for receiving SMS from the system, if this functionality is activated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment: Free text field for additional information about the user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;user-type&#34;&gt;User type&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Name and roles for all user types may be altered by the System administrator. User types may also be added and removed. The capabilities of a user type are defined by the system roles assigned to it. A user must have one user type for each department the user is attached to. For a logged in user with multiple user types, only the roles attached to the user type of the department the user is currently logged in at, will be active. In the Standard version four user types are preconfigured: Manager, Case handler and Reviewer have the complete interface, while Worker has the Simplified interface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;manager-1&#34;&gt;Manager&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have full access to the system in the standard version. Can have limited or increased access with the help of system roles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;case-handler&#34;&gt;Case handler&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Same access rights as the Manager, but the access to Admin is replaced by Preferences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managers and Case handlers appear automatically as possible recipients (case handlers) for messages under Messages/NC / Message process within their department. If it must be possible to send messages across the organisation, for example from the Health Department to the Technical department, at least one user of the user type Manager or Case handler in that department must be set under the tab Admin / Rules, Rule type &amp;ldquo;Additional case handlers&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;reviewer-1&#34;&gt;Reviewer&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have the same read access as Managers. They can only edit their own information, but may comment on all cases they can read. They appear automatically as possible recipients of the messages under Inform in the Messages/NC / Message process on their department. Reviewers may only register new messages on the department they are registered on, even though they have the navigator. They have the tab Preferences instead of Admin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;worker&#34;&gt;Worker&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They have their own simple interface that only allows access to their own information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;worker-1&#34;&gt;Worker&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;User type that in the standard version gives the users a simple interface, from which they can access only their own cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;action-status&#34;&gt;Action status&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An action in Qm+ has an status that shows where it is in the handling process. The status of an action changes under Action process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under planning: The action is being planned. Text fields must be filled out, categorisation and cost must be set and one or more users must be made responsible for executing the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under execution: The action has been sent to the person(s) who will execute it. When all the persons responsible for executing the action have checked out the field &amp;ldquo;Executed&amp;quot;and have written their comments, it can be sent for approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under approval: The action is waiting for approval from the person who created it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approved: The action has been approved and can no longer be changed. Super users with the system role content administrator can still make changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An action under execution or under approval may be sent backwards in the process by using the &amp;laquo; buttons in the status field of the Action process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;activity-group&#34;&gt;Activity group&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Activities are organised in activity groups. This organisation has no influence on the system beyond the fact that it makes it easier to identify activities when there are many of them. In the Calendar under the Activity plan, activities are shown per activity group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;activity-report&#34;&gt;Activity report&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An activity report can be used to write a final report for an activity. The activity report can be written by pressing the Report button under Comments to the activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Which message form will be used in the activity report is determined under Edit list information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Activity reports are not included in the standard version and must be ordered specifically.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;alternative-answer&#34;&gt;Alternative answer&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An alternative answer is an answer you can choose to a question in a survey form. All the alternative answers you can choose from for one question are called an alternative group. Managed under Edit alternative answers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-3&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Number: Determines the sorting of the alternative answers in the alternative group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Text: The displayed text for that alternative answer. Each alternative answer may have one text for each enabled language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;alternative-groups-overview&#34;&gt;Alternative groups overview&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All the alternative groups belong to an alternative groups overview. This is used only to distinguish between alternative groups when editing alternative answers and under the tab Alternative groups. Managed from the tab Alternative groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;case-handler-1&#34;&gt;Case handler&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Case handler is a user type in the standard version in Qm+ that has approximately the same rights as the user type manager. That means full access to read and modify all cases within his/her remit, as well as reports via Reports and the Activity plan. A case handler does not have access to Admin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;category-dependency&#34;&gt;Category dependency&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A category dependency is used for controlling when a category is shown in a message form. Only categories without dependencies and categories that have all their dependencies satisfied are shown in the message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A category dependency is only used for the actual message form it is set up for. A category may only have one dependency against each of the other categories in that message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A category satisfies its dependencies when it both:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;satisfies all &amp;ldquo;And&amp;rdquo; dependencies. If it has no &amp;ldquo;And&amp;rdquo; dependencies it is considered as satisfied.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;satisfies at least one &amp;ldquo;Or&amp;rdquo; dependency or it has no &amp;ldquo;Or&amp;rdquo; dependencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managed under Edit category dependency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;checklist&#34;&gt;Checklist&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A checklist is a list that is displayed with checkboxes in front of the question. To be able to edit alternative answers, the list type survey form must be used. A checklist is intended to be used as a &amp;ldquo;find the error list&amp;rdquo;. That lists a series of common errors within the area to be examined. The users then check the point in the list if they know of the error. See list for explanation of data fields.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;comment-message&#34;&gt;Comment message&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A comment message is an additional text response to a question in a list. Comment messages are registered in a normal message form. Only the first text field in the message form that is connected to the list will show as a comment field inside the list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Comment messages can be handled in the same way as the other messages. In the standard version, comment messages do not appear under Inbox unless someone has transferred them to a case handler, set a deadline or created an action for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show comment list in Activity plan is used to get an overview of the comment messages for an activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can get an overview of all comment messages from the tab Comment reports under Reports or from the Comments tab under Archive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;default-case-handler&#34;&gt;Default case handler&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a message form has a default case handler, the messages registered with this message form will appear on the Cases I am responsible for page of the default case handler instead of the Manager of the department where the message was registered. The message will still be registered on the department it was registered and will appear under Reports and Search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the same message form is set up with multiple default case handlers with overlapping departments, the user registering the message will be able to choose between them from a drop-down menu during registration. In the registration screen, there is also a checkbox for whether to send an email to the selected case handler when the message is registered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;department&#34;&gt;Department&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A department is a set of information that identifies a physical location or an organisational unit that will be used as the reporting unit in Qm+. Active departments can be selected in the Navigator. Managed under Admin / Organisation / Edit department. If a department is moved within the organisational structure, all associated data and records will automatically follow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Function under Organisation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields-1&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department name: The name used for the department in the system. Will appear in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subdepartment of: The department under which this department appears in the Navigator. This department will inherit the lists, the message forms, the documents and the activities from the department above it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;advanced-options-1&#34;&gt;Advanced options&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The department&amp;rsquo;s roles: The roles associated with this department.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roles associated with a department apply to all users of the active department. That means all employees of that department and all other users who have selected that department in the navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roles associated with a department are used to control the accessibility of documents, forms and activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The department&amp;rsquo;s main tasks: Departments may be related to categories in a category group classified as Tasks. This is meant to visualize the department&amp;rsquo;s main tasks, and has currently no system effect beyond that.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;display-criterion&#34;&gt;Display criterion&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A display criterion is a criterion that can be set on a question or a group of questions in a survey form. The most common use is to set up a question to show only if a particular alternative answer is selected on a previous question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display criteria are set for each survey form under Edit alternative answers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;behaviour&#34;&gt;Behaviour&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific group, Element = None, Alternative = None: A checkbox appears before the group name with the text &amp;ldquo;Show&amp;rdquo; when the list is filled out. This box must be checked, in order for the questions in this group to show.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific group, specific Element, Alternative = None: The question shows only if the particular question is not answered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Specific group, specific Element, specific Alternative: The question shows only if the particular question is answered with the specific alternative answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display criteria work for the list version and the single question view.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;document&#34;&gt;Document&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A document is a text written in Qm+, a reference to a file, a reference to a web page or a folder. Shown in the table under info for all users who have access to them, according to the document&amp;rsquo;s department and roles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Managed under Edit document data. A simple version control also exists on that page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-4&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: Used to identify the document in tables and overviews.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document type:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Written document: The document is written and maintained in the internal text editor of Qm+. When the document is opened, it will automatically get a meta-table that contains data about the document. The table shows who has created the document, when it was changed, the customer&amp;rsquo;s logo and possibly the hearing status it has. The table can be customized on a per customer level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link: The document is a link to a page on the Internet, a document written in Qm+ or a file uploaded to Qm+.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;File: The document is a file that was uploaded to Qm+ and stored on the server of QmPlus AS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folder: The document is only a folder that contains other documents under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process chart: The document is written and maintained in the Process chart setup page of Qm+ and can be displayed in two modes, Process chart and Responsibility matrix. When the document is opened, it will automatically get a meta-table that contains data about the document, identical to the one added to documents of type Written document. After a process chart is saved, it is not possible to change the type of the document again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document group: The document&amp;rsquo;s group. Determines in which box the document will appear under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tab: Determines under which tab the document will appear under Info. Appears only if this functionality is turned on. In the standard version, all documents are shown under the tab Managing documents under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subdocument of: A subdocument will be shown only when the document above it is extended by holding the cursor over the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon. Make sure to choose something in this menu after you have selected the Document group and the Document tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Address: Where is the document. If it is a file that was uploaded, the address field will be set automatically. Do not make changes to it afterwards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: The document will be available from the selected department and its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shown for subdepartments?: If no, the document will only appear under Info when the selected department in the &amp;ldquo;From department&amp;rdquo; is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created by: The name of the user who has created this document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version: Version number. Shows how many times there were changes made on the document. It will not be updated if the change is done outside Qm+.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roles: An unlimited number of roles can be associated with the document. A user must have at least one of these in order to be able to see the document under the Info page. Does not affect the availability of the document in the message forms or lists to which the document is attached.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Last modified: Date when the document was last modified.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;filling-out-pdf-forms&#34;&gt;Filling out PDF forms&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;purpose&#34;&gt;Purpose&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has been requested that the details of a message which will be reported with the help of a PDF form, should be automatically filled in. If a form has been linked to a PDF, the user will have a new opportunity to select a message form for filling data into the PDF. After the PDF document is opened, the data are already copied in the correct fields and the user can fill in the rest of the form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;layout&#34;&gt;Layout&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order for the data of a form to be able to be exported to a PDF form, the fields must be manually connected to the fields of the PDF. Unfortunately, for the moment, this can only be done directly in the database, ie, the users must ask Qm+ to do it for them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to connect a form to a PDF, we need the PDF and the message it will be connected to. In addition we need an accurate description of which fields in the PDF will be connected to which fields in the message.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;gps-coordinates&#34;&gt;GPS coordinates&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Map.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 GPS coordinates is a tab under Edit message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messages registered through the mobile application send the GPS coordinates of the location of the mobile device at the time of registration. Use this page to decide if these coordinates will appear in the Message process page and in the pdf reports. More options will appear in this page soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;list&#34;&gt;List&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A list is a form used to collect information. Lists are managed under Admin / Forms and are sent out from the Activity plan. The appearance of a list is determined by the selected list type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-5&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: The name of a list can be set once for every language that is activated in the system. Appears only for customers who have multiple active languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List name: Used to identify the list in tables and menus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List type: Used to organise the lists in various overviews under Admin. Has no practical significance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered by department: The department where the list was created. A list can be used from the department where it was created and from its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached message form: The message form that is used to store comments on the list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached category: The category which will be selected in the attached message form when the comment is written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached report form: The message form that will be used to save reports to an activity where the list has been used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached report category: The category which will be selected in the attached message form when the report is written.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The report form and the report categories are not included in the standard version but can be activated for all customers who want them. In this case, contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:drift@qmplus.com&#34;&gt;drift@qmplus.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;List comment: A textual comment that will appear at the top of list when it is filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached documents: A link above the list that opens the selected document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;list-version&#34;&gt;List version&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display type for lists. Used mainly for checklists and risk analysis lists. Shows all the questions in a list. Opportunity to comment comes up on page two after Save is pressed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All lists that appear when you log in to Qm+ in the normal way (not when logging in via a link in an e-mail that takes you directly to the list), are using the list version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;periodic-activity&#34;&gt;Periodic activity&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A periodic activity is used when you want to schedule a periodic execution of an activity forward in time. The period is how frequently the activity will be carried out, for example, daily, weekly, annually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The period and the individual dates can be managed under Periodic activity setup, and the other activity data under Edit activity. Individual dates for a periodic activity can be deleted under Activities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;priority&#34;&gt;Priority&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Messages in Qm+ may have different priorities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low: Highlighted in green.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Medium: Highlighted in yellow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High: highlighted in red.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An action gets the same priority as the message attached to it with the highest priority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;repetitive-activity&#34;&gt;Repetitive activity&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A repetitive activity is an activity that can be filled out an unlimited number of times by each participant. Can also be used for registration of anonymous external surveys where all responses are registered on the same user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;risk-analysis-list&#34;&gt;Risk analysis list&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A risk analysis list is a list that is displayed with a drop-down menu for the probability and a drop-down menu for the consequence of each question. See list for explanation of data fields.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;risk-message&#34;&gt;Risk message&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Risk messages are messages used to create a risk overview for your company. It is up to the company whether the risk messages should be handled or if they should only be registered and stored in the archive. Our recommendation is that they are not handled, only updated annually. Risk messages can only be closed by QmPlus AS (as an exception), as they should not normally be handled. Messages registered here do not appear in the Inbox unless you use Message process to activate them. The message type risk message is not enabled in the standard version.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;role&#34;&gt;Role&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A role can be assigned to users, user types, departments, activities, message forms and documents. They provide rights and restrictions. Generally one can say that a user or a user&amp;rsquo;s department must have the same role as an activity, a message form or a document in order to have access to it. Common roles can be set by the customer&amp;rsquo;s super user.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roles are sorted in role groups and managed under Edit role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A special type of roles called system roles give extended rights for use of Qm+. System roles are set by QmPlus AS and they can be assigned to some super users. This is an advanced functionality and is usually not given to new customers. Contact &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:drift@qmplus.com&#34;&gt;drift@qmplus.com&lt;/a&gt; if you need this right or if you have questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data-6&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: A role can have one name for each language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;rules-submenu-message-form&#34;&gt;Rules submenu message form&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Wrench.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Rules submenu message form is a tab under Edit message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use this page to get an overview of the rules which are associated with the message form. See Rules for a more detailed description of the table contents and functionality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that a message registered with a message form without case handlers follows the normal procedure and appears in the Inbox / My current cases of the nearest manager. In most cases this is the best solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;sub-activity&#34;&gt;Sub-activity&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An activity can have sub-activities. They have no effect other than the fact that they are visually grouped together under Activities and Calendar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;survey-form&#34;&gt;Survey form&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A type of list. Provides full flexibility to change the answers and comments for all questions. When used as a traditional survey, it is often worth using the display type &amp;ldquo;single question view&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-action-process&#34;&gt;The action process&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The action process is the process from when an action is created until it is approved and closed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Followed up through the Action process page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under planning: All actions start with this status. In this phase, the action is being planned. First give a name to the action so that it becomes easy to identify it later, and enter the budget if you use this field. The text fields Corrective action and How to prevent repetition must be filled out so that those who will execute the action will know what to do. The action categories may also be selected now. The last thing you have to do is to select those who should execute the action and give them a deadline. This is done in the mandatory panel Persons responsible. Click on Send to execution &amp;raquo; or the &amp;raquo; button in the Status panel to save the action and change its status to Under execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under execution: In this phase, the work described in the action will be executed. If the time registration fields are enabled, the executors can log the hours they have spent carrying out the action per day. Then those who carried out the action must tick the Executed box. They can also write a comment in the Comment field and fill in the Actual cost if they know it. When all the changes have been done, use the button Send to approval &amp;raquo; or the &amp;raquo; button in the Status panel. This saves the action and change its status to Under approval.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under approval: Here the person who created the action will make sure everything is in order before (s)he approves the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Approved: An approved action is closed and locked and can not be changed except by users with the system role content administrator. Comments can still be sent out to all involved users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Department cases</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/inbox/tabs/department_cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/inbox/tabs/department_cases/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Department cases shows cases that the department that is selected in the Navigator has to work with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pink cases are messages, yellow cases are actions and blue-gray cases are hearings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;options&#34;&gt;Options&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Register new message: Select a message form to register a new message. Opens the Edit message page. The message forms are displayed as individual buttons if there are up to 4 different forms. If there are more, the button 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


Register new message must be pressed first. This opens a list of all active message forms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All messages drop-down menu: If you select a message form, only cases originating from such a form are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/LeftArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Change page: The arrows are used to change the page when there are more than 20 cases that can be displayed in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Sort_down.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/No_sort.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Sorting: The table is sorted by the column with the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Sort_down.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


. Click on 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/No_sort.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to sort on another column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_green.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


, 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_yellow.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


, 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_red.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Priority: Symbolize low, medium and high priority respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;main-table&#34;&gt;Main table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you click on a line of the main table, the selected case will open in its handling page. Messages open in the Message process page, actions open in the Action process page and hearings open in the Reply to a hearing page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Extra Information and History: Hold the cursor over the + symbol to get more information about the case. Currently, only for messages and actions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message form: Which message form was used to create the case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered: The date when the case was registered. For messages when they were registered, for actions when they were created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due: For messages this is the handling deadline, for actions this is the execution and approval deadline.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Description: For messages this is the text in the first text field of the message, for actions this is their name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_green.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


, 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_yellow.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


, 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Flag_red.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 symbolize low, medium and high priority respectively. For actions, this is the priority of the attached message to them with the highest priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: The status of the case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered on department: The department where the case was originally registered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current case handler: Depends on the type and status of the case.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blank: The case is registered on this department and no responsible person has been assigned to it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;The name of a user&gt;: This user is the assigned responsible person for the case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;Under planning&amp;raquo;: The name of the user who has created the action and has the main responsibility for it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;Under execution&amp;raquo;: The names of the users who will execute the action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;Under approval&amp;raquo;: The name of the user who has created the action and is responsible for approving it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;On hearing&amp;raquo;: The names of the users who will participate in the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With status &amp;laquo;For approval&amp;raquo;: The name of the user who will approve the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;which-cases-are-shown-in-the-table&#34;&gt;Which cases are shown in the table?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages sent to a user in the department which is selected in the Navigator via Send to case handler under Message process or via the Early case process under Edit message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For managers:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages registered on the selected department if that has a manager, that have not been assigned to another responsible person.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Messages registered on a subordinate department, where there isn&amp;rsquo;t a manager and have not been assigned to another responsible person. Messages registered on departments without a manager will be moved upwards in the organisation hierarchy and will appear in the Inbox on the first department above that has a manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions under planning created by a user of the department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions under execution that will be executed by a user of the department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actions for approval that will be approved by a user of the department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearings that are on hearing in which a user of the department will participate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearings that are for approval which a user of the department will approve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note that messages other users have registered which were made with message forms that have a role with the &amp;ldquo;See messages&amp;rdquo; limitation, will not be shown here unless the logged in user has the same role or the system role See all messages attached to him / her or to the user type the user is logged in with. Messages which the user himself / herself has registered will be shown.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Dialog</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/dialog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/dialog/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: The status of the message and who is responsible for it, are shown at the top of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feedback to case handler: Here you can write a text and send it by email. The sent text will also be registered on the case and will follow it. It will appear in this screen in the table below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send email to: Select the person who should receive the message. The list is sorted by department and includes:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The nearest manager(s) is (are) always displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The current case handler of the selected message, if one has been set.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anyone who has sent a message to the logged in user about the specific case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A table that shows the previous communication on this issue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Do you have comments?</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/do_you_have_comments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/do_you_have_comments/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;It is only possible to register one comment message per question.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Back to list: Sends you back to Filling out a list form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Done: Sends you back to Fill out and results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the Edit message form to write a new comment message on the question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the Edit message form to edit a comment message on the question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document content</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_content/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;These are documents that are written directly into Qm+ using its document editing tool. Opens from the page Edit document data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TinyMCE is used to create the text editor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spell-check&#34;&gt;Spell check&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If your browser has activated spell check, words that the spell checker considers to be misspelled will be highlighted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press the Ctrl key at the same time as you right click on the highlighted word to get spelling suggestions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;editor-buttons&#34;&gt;Editor buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The functions in this editor work in a similar way as in other document editing tools. Note in particular:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Bullist.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Bulleted (unordered) list: Select some text and click on this button to turn the text into a bulleted list. Click on the arrow to the right of the icon to select the bullet shape.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Numlist.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Numbered (ordered) list: Select some text and click on this button to turn the text into a numbered list. Click on the arrow to the right of the icon to select the number type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Outdent.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Decrease indent (outdent): Allows you to remove a &lt;tab&gt; character or combine a sub-list with the rest of the list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Indent.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Increase indent: Allows you to add a &lt;tab&gt; character or to create a sub-list of items in a list. For a sub-list the numbering starts anew. One can have different types of numbering in the list and the sub-list. This can be set using the arrow to the right of the Numbered list or the Bulleted list icon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Insert / Edit link: Select some text and then click on this button to turn the text into a link. You will then see a dialogue box where the link address can be entered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Unlink.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Remove link (unlink): Select an existing link and then click on this button to turn the link into plain text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Html.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit HTML source code: Opens a separate window where the document&amp;rsquo;s HTML code can be edited directly. This should be done only if you know HTML. Remember to click on the Update button when you are finished editing the HTML code. For explanation of the various HTML tags look here: Overview of HTML elements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document data</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_data/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;document-name-and-type&#34;&gt;Document name and type&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: The name of the document. Can be up to 100 characters long.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information: Short text (up to 500 characters) with information about the document. This text appears as a tooltip when you hover over the document name in Info, in message forms and lists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document type: Τhe type of this document.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a document: Used if you wish to create (write) a document directly in Qm+. The document is saved as an HTML document and has some formatting options. The text edit field uses TinyMCE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link: Used if you wish to link to a resource on the internet or to a document on a local file server. Documents that are not accessible from the internet will not be indexed in our search engine and will appear as a Link Error under Documents. Make sure that the address entered is a valid http or https address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;File: Used if you want to upload a file from your local computer to the Qm+ server. This creates a copy of the file on the server. To make changes in the file, it must be edited locally and then uploaded again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folder: Used to create a folder structure under Info. Can not be opened as a document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process chart: Used when you want to create a process chart in Qm+. When you save a document with this type, the tab Process chart setup becomes available and you are no longer able to change the document type of this document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;choose-where-the-document-will-be-shown-under-info&#34;&gt;Choose where the document will be shown under INFO&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document departments. Table that shows the departments where the document will be shown.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department. The document will be visible under Info and under Admin / Documents on the departments that will be set here. Use the &amp;ldquo;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Add department&amp;rdquo; button to get a new drop-down menu in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shown for subdepartments. If this is checked, the document will also be visible under Info from the subdepartments of the department which is selected in the &amp;ldquo;From department&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delete. Only active if the document is associated with more than one department. Click on the Delete department icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to delete the association with the specific department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tab: Determines under which tab the document will appear under Info. Mandatory field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document group: The document&amp;rsquo;s group. Determines in which box the document will appear under Info. Mandatory field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subdocument of: A subdocument will not be shown under Info, until the document above it is expanded by holding the cursor over the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public document: If this is checked, the document will be available to everyone and no authentication will be required to open it. Applies only to documents of type &amp;ldquo;Write a document&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Link&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;File&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position: Used only if the alphabetical sorting is turned off. Normally you can ignore this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;customer-specific-document-heading-fields&#34;&gt;Customer specific document heading fields&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These fields must be ordered separately. Used to add extra fields that will be displayed in the document heading. Only applicable for documents written in Qm+. Possible field types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Free text.
Date.
Department. Displays a drop-down menu that contains all departments. This may be role filtered, which means that only departments with a predefined role will be shown.
User. Displays a drop-down menu that contains all users. This may be role filtered, which means that only users with a predefined role will be shown.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;status&#34;&gt;Status&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This section appears only for documents that have been saved at least once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version: The version of the document. Displayed as x.y, where x is the main version number and y is the edit number.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The main version number is increased by 1 each time the button &amp;ldquo;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Disc_multiple.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create new version&amp;rdquo; is pressed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The edit number is increased by 1 each time this page is saved and either the name, the document content if this is a document written in Qm+, or the document address has changed or a new document has been uploaded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The edit number starts at 1 for each new version that is created. The edit number in previous versions of Qm+ was referred to as the revision number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The version number is displayed as a link that you can click on. It opens the document in that version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the version shown on the page is newer than the published version of the document or the document has never been published, the button 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_lightning.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Publish will appear. This button stores any changes made in the document and sets the current version as the published one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are in a version of a document which has a newer version, you will be notified by the icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Exclamation.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and the text &amp;ldquo;This document has a newer version&amp;rdquo;. This text is a link that opens the newer version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents that have a newer version can be changed, but you cannot create new versions of them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Published version. If the version of the document which is shown on the page is the actual published version, i.e. the one that appears under Info, the text &amp;ldquo;This is the published version&amp;rdquo; shows. If not, the version number of the actual published version of the document is displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created by: The name of the user who has created this document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latest edit by: The name of the user who changed the document last.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing status for this version: Appears only if the selected version is associated with a hearing. Displays the status of the hearing and links to Reply to a hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document address: Only shown for saved documents. If you want another document in Qm+ to refer to this document, you may use this address as a link. This address can now also be used outside Qm+ and, for documents written in Qm+ (Document type: Write a document) or for uploaded files (Document type: File), it will always take you to the latest published version. If you are not already logged into Qm+, you will be prompted for your username and password in order to see the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;audit&#34;&gt;Audit&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activate regular audit. You should check this when you want a user to be warned on a regular basis that the document should be audited. The following fields described in this section are shown when this box is checked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Warning date for audit. The date when the user will be notified of the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit interval. The period between each warning. When a document, for which the audit due date has passed, is audited, the warning date is increased by the value in this field. If the document gets audited before the audit due date, the warning date will not be automatically updated. If you wish to update the warning date in this case, you will have to do so manually.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit responsible. The user who receives the document audit warning in his / her Inbox.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;extra-attributes&#34;&gt;Extra attributes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document is a template. Yes / No. Standard No. Only applicable for documents of the type &amp;ldquo;Write a document&amp;rdquo;. A template document is an outline or start of a document, such as a set of standard headlines. Template documents that are saved and published can be inserted into, preferably new, documents from the Document content tab by all users. Template documents do not show under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document heading type. Appears only for those who have the option for selectable document heading type set. Applies only to documents of the type &amp;ldquo;Write a document.&amp;rdquo; Determines which of the available document heading types will be used for this document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document groups</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_groups/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here one can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s document groups.
Deactivated document groups do not appear under Info and no document can be assigned to them. Documents that belong to a deactivated document group do not appear under Info either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choice of department: The table shows either all the document groups created at the department which is selected in the Navigator or the document groups created at the department which is selected in the Navigator and those created by its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New document group: Opens the Edit document group screen to create a new document group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the Edit document group screen to change an existing document group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Deactivates or activates the document group depending on whether you are under Document groups or under Deactivated document groups respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document tab</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/info/document_tab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/info/document_tab/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Managed under Edit document tab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Documents are assigned to document tabs under Edit document data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;data&#34;&gt;Data&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: The name of a document tab can be registered once for every language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: Used to identify the document tab in tables and overviews. A document tab can have one name for each language that is activated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position: The position of the document tab under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: The document tab will appear under Info from the selected department and from its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shown for subdepartments: If no, the document tab will only appear under Info when the department selected under &amp;ldquo;From department&amp;rdquo; is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subtab of: Used, if this tab should be a subtab. Then it will appear at a new level of tabs, under the tab that is selected here. Tabs with underlying tabs are not allowed to have their own documents.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information: Text that appears when you hold the cursor over the tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Roles: A document tab with roles is only shown under Info if the user opening Info or the selected department in the navigator has at least one of the roles the document tab has.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document tabs</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_tabs/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here one can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s document tabs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deactivated document tabs do not appear under Info and no documents can be assigned to them. Documents that belong to a deactivated document tab do not appear under Info either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New document tab: Opens the Edit document tab screen to create a new document tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the Edit document tab screen to edit an existing document tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Deactivates or activates the document tab depending on whether you are under Document tabs or Deactivated document tabs respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/View.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Used to open a document tab which you do not have the right to change. One has the right to change the document tabs created from the selected department in the Navigator and the underlying departments of that&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Documents</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/admin/tabs/documents/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/admin/tabs/documents/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;From here you can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s documents, document groups and document tabs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode-s0-hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a super user / manager I can add documents (laws, procedures, etc.): Click on the button New document at the bottom of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can create new Document tabs and new Document groups.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents: Displays documents. Submenus:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Published documents. These are shown under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unpublished documents. These are not shown under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated published documents. These are not shown under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated unpublished documents. These are not shown under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document groups: Displays document groups. Submenus:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document groups. These are shown under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated document groups. These are not shown under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tabs: Displays document tabs. Submenus:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tabs. These are shown under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deactivated document tabs. These are not shown under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Documents submenu</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/documents_submenu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/documents_submenu/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;From here you can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The document names function as links. Click on a document name to open the document. Especially for documents created in Qm+: You can either open the HTML version by clicking on the document name, or you can get a PDF version of the document by clicking on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon on the right of the document name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deactivated documents do not appear under Info and cannot be attached to lists, message forms or activities. Already attached documents will still be shown there even if they are deactivated. Attached documents can not be deleted. Unpublished documents are not shown under Info either. If a document has both a published and a newer unpublished version, the published version will be displayed under Info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode-s1-hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a new document click the button &amp;ldquo;New document&amp;rdquo; at the bottom of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit a document / send it out on a hearing: Click on the yellow &amp;ldquo;Edit document data&amp;rdquo;-icon on the right side of the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the next page you can select between the tabs Version overview, Hearing overview, Audit overview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department selection: The table shows either all the documents created at the department which is selected in the Navigator or the documents created at the department which is selected in the Navigator and those from its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tab selection: The table shows only the documents that belong to the selected document tab. If the option &amp;ldquo;Show documents from all document tabs&amp;rdquo; is selected, all the documents are shown independent of the document tab they belong to. Please note that only documents that belong to active document tabs are shown. The drop-down does not contain any deactivated document tabs either, but contains tabs from all departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document group selection: The table shows only the documents that belong to the selected document group. If the option &amp;ldquo;Show documents from all document groups&amp;rdquo; is selected, all the documents are shown independent of the document group they belong to. Please note that only documents that belong to active document groups are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display mode:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document Information. Default, shows an overview of where in the structure the document belongs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit information. Displays the warning date for the next audit for the document and information about the previous / ongoing audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New document: Opens the Edit document data screen to create a new document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Icons are used to symbolize different types of documents:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_world.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Link to the online version of the document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Lovdata_icon.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Link to a page from Lovdata&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_word.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Word document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 PDF document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_excel.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Excel document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_powerpoint.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Powerpoint document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_text.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Document created in Qm+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Shape_align_center.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Document of type Process chart, created in Qm+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Unknown or Blank document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder_page_white.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Folder. Can not be opened, used only to create a document structure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;edit&#34;&gt;Edit&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Edit document data. Opens the Edit document data screen to edit an existing document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Date_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Create read and understood activity. This opens the New activity page under Activity plan and automatically sets the Activity group, the Activity name, the Attached list, the time period (From - To), the Activity distribution and the attached document. It is possible to use other lists than the default one for Read and understood. If someone wants to use another list as default, they will have to contact QmPlus AS. If you click the Create read and understood activity button of a document that has subdocuments, the subdocuments will also be added to the activity automatically.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Deactivate / Activate document. Deactivates or activates the document depending on whether you are under Documents or Deactivated documents respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Delete document. Deletes the document. Only visible for deactivated documents that are not attached to other elements in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;status&#34;&gt;Status&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_error.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Not indexed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_medal.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tag_blue_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: On hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Ok.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Error.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Indexing error. This may mean that the document is not available or is in a format that our indexing engine has not been able to decipher. It may happen that even normal formats like .pdf and .doc fail. If the link opens the document correctly, the error only means that the document will not appear in any search results if you do a free text search under Info. Links to intranet pages or other sites that the search engine has no access to, will always give indexing errors.
Note: The symbol § in a link is often not recognised by the search engine, which leads to an indexing error. We suggest replacing it with its equivalent HTML code, which is %C2%A7.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Exclamation.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: The document has a newer unpublished / existing published version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Date.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: The document is part of a Read and understood activity. If you leave the cursor over the icon, you will see a popup with information about the last Read and understood activity for the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Documents submenu message form</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/forms/tabs/documents_submenu_message_form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/forms/tabs/documents_submenu_message_form/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page is used for managing documents in the message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;administration-of-documents&#34;&gt;Administration of documents&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tab. Only documents that belong to the document tab which is selected here are displayed in the drop-down menu below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document: Select the document that you want to assign to the message form and then click on the button 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Add. Please note that if you add a document that has subdocuments, all its subdocuments will also be added to the message form. If you want to remove a document from the message form, click on the respective Delete icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit activity</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/functions/edit_activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/activity/functions/edit_activity/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity group: Select which activity group this activity will belong to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activity name: Identifies the activity in tables and overviews. Also used as a heading when an attached list is filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached list: If a list should be filled out, it is selected here. The lists in the drop-down menu are sorted by list type. This field cannot be changed after someone has answered the activity.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show printer friendly version: Opens the printer friendly version of the selected list. Click on this icon when a list is selected to see how it looks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From: The date and time when the activity starts. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Calendar_icon.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to open a calendar for date selection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To: The date and time when the activity ends. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Calendar_icon.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to open a calendar for date selection.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes made in the fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cog_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show / 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cog_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Hide advanced options: Displays or hides the advanced options.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;advanced-options&#34;&gt;Advanced options&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These are options that come up when the button 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cog_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show advanced options is used. The advanced options are hidden by using the button 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cog_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Hide advanced options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;fields-1&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show for the language: Drop-down menu with the languages that are activated in the system. - The name of the activity can be set once for every available language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Activity distribution (Optional):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Normal: The answers of the participants are registered on their own department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit: Those who participate can answer the activity once for each department they have access to. If the activity is repetitive, they can answer it an unlimited number of times per department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Read and understood: A Read and understood activity is used to distribute a document and get a confirmation that it has been read and understood. Read and understood activities behave exactly as usual activities, with the exception that they cannot be sent out periodically, repetitively or anonymously. These options are therefore hidden when the option Read and understood is selected as the Activity distribution. Those who want this feature turned on must contact QmPlus AS.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The subordinate departments will do the activity: Check this box if the subdepartments of the selected department will also participate in the activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;How often will the activity be performed?: Drop-down menu to determine the type of the activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One time: Common activity that can be filled out once by all the users who can participate.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeating: Repetitive activity. Can be filled out an unlimited number of times by each participant. Used when you do not know in advance how many times a list will be needed and filled out. Can also be used for anonymous external surveys.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Periodic: Used when you want to schedule a periodic execution of an activity forward in time. Set the From and To fields to include the entire period you want to schedule. After you make all the other selections in this page you need to press Save. Then you will go to the page Periodic activity setup. There you can set the period, e.g. daily, weekly, annually. This option is not recommended for the first time you create an activity. It is only appropriate to make periodic activities if you are certain that the attached list is not going to change within that period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do you want an email reminder before the activity is due?: The system can send an email to the person who created the activity at the number of days before it ends that will be selected in the drop-down menu. The email will contain information such as how many people participated and how many should participate, as well as a link to Follow up where you can write and send a reminder email to those who have not yet answered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send new reminder?:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Should an email reminder be sent to the participants before the activity is due?:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Send new reminder?:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This activity is answered anonymously: Checkbox that makes the activity anonymous. Comments on anonymous activities will be anonymous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Number of answers before the result is visible: Appears only when the anonymity box is checked. The number selected here controls how many answers a single department must have before a graph is shown for this department under Graphs for the list. The starting value of this drop-down can be changed using the system setting ANONYMOUSPARTICIPATIONMINIMUMLIMIT.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display as list: The list will be answered in the list version view. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon to see how the selected list looks like in this display type. Should be used for checklists and risk analysis lists. Can be used for survey forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display as series of single questions (reminder link only): Τhe list will be answered as a series of single questions. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon to see how the selected list looks like in this display type. Used to give survey forms the more traditional questionnaire look. &amp;ldquo;Reminder link only&amp;rdquo; means that this display type will only be used when the person who will answer the list has come to it by clicking on the link in the email that is sent out as a reminder for the activity. Otherwise, if for example you are logged into Qm+ as usual, the list version will always be used when you try to fill out the list.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Display as control list: In this view, there is one checkbox per day per question and the alternative answers do not appear at all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roles that will perform the activity: When you associate roles to an activity, only users that have at least one of these roles can participate in it. If no roles are selected, all within the selected departments can participate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Document tab selection: Only documents which belong to the document tab that is selected here are shown below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Add documents to the activity: Documents attached to the activity will be shown at the top of the attached list as blue clickable links when it is answered. Used if those who will answer need to have reference material or additional information available when they answer the list. Please note that if you add a document that has subdocuments, all its subdocuments will also be added to the activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;buttons-1&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;laquo; Add: Adds one or more of the items which are selected in the right panel to the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove &amp;raquo;: Removes one or more of the items which are selected in the left panel to the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit alternative answers</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/edit_alternative_answers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/edit_alternative_answers/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Edit alternative answers is used for setting alternative answers and display criteria for questions in survey forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode-s0-hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can add answer groups in the questionnaire. Click on the drop-down menu with the Alternative groups and select one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the alternative group you are looking for is not in the drop-down menu: Click on &amp;ldquo;New alternative group&amp;rdquo; at the bottom of the page. You will find your new group at the bottom.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can select if the alternative answers will be Text, Multiple choice or Single choice. Click in Order / Answer type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menu&#34;&gt;Drop-down menu&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Default alternative group for this list: Drop-down menu that sets the alternative group which will be used in this list. The corresponding Choose button updates the list below according to the choice made here. Note that all changes of alternative answers you have already done in this list will be overwritten when you do this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;list-table&#34;&gt;List table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The table shows all the questions in the list and is used for assigning alternative groups to each question. Display criteria can also be set for all questions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Accept.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 / 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Asterisk_orange.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the submenu to edit the display criteria for this question. 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Accept.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 means that the question does not have a display criterion and will always be shown. 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Asterisk_orange.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 means that the question has a display criterion and that it will only be shown for the user who answers the list when the display criterion is fulfilled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Group / Element name: Dark rows show groups, light rows show questions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Order / Answer type: Sorting applies to all questions in a group, answer type applies to each question.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternative group: The alternative group that applies to the current question. If the alternative group is changed for a group and the Save button is used, all the questions in that group will be assigned to this alternative group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;alternative-answers&#34;&gt;Alternative answers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the same table that can be found under Alternative groups.
Buttons&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_gear.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit list information. Takes you to the Edit list information screen to edit the information on the selected checklist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit list content. Takes you to the Edit list content screen to edit the questions of the selected checklist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Preview. Opens the preview window to see how the list looks in the printer friendly version. In this window you can also choose to see the list in list form or as a series of single questions which is how it will look when it will be filled out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit alternative group</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/edit_alternative_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/edit_alternative_group/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Used to edit alternative groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Language: The alternative answers in an alternative group can be set once for each language that is enabled in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternative groups overview: Every alternative group belongs to an alternative groups overview. Here you can choose which one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Key_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New alternative answer: Opens a text field where you can write the name of a new alternative answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Key_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete alternative answer: Appears only when you click on an alternative answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes you have made. Use this once you have entered a new or edited an existing alternative answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes this page and sends you back to Alternative groups or Edit alternative answers depending on where you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click on the text of an alternative answer to select it. The row in the table will be highlighted in red. Now you can edit the text or use the button Delete alternative answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/SmallArrowUpFilled.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Move this alternative answer up in the alternative group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/SmallArrowDownFilled.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Move this alternative answer down in the alternative group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit alternative groups overview</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/edit_alternative_groups_overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/list/functions/edit_alternative_groups_overview/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Used for editing the name of an alternative groups overview.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Show for the language: Drop-down menu for the language. An alternative groups overview may have one name per language that is enabled in the system.
Alternative groups overview name: Write the name of the alternative groups overview.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the active window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes that have been made.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes this screen and sends you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit category</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/admin/functions/edit_category/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/admin/functions/edit_category/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here you can manage the data of categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcode-s0-hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Categories tab gives me the possibility to create new or edit existing Categories. (They will later be added to a message form).
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Select a category group. Then&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;enter the name of the new category. if applicable,&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;predefine the cost (which will be automatically added when you select this category in a message form).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can decide from which department (in the navigator) the category will be visible in a message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Attention! The same message form can have different content depending on the location in the Navigator you have selected! If you want a pop-up for this category: Write this in the information text field.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show for the language: The name of a category can be set once for every language that is activated in the system. Appears only for customers who have multiple active languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category group: The category&amp;rsquo;s group. The category group type of the category group determines how this category will look like in a message form. A text at the bottom of this screen describes the type of the selected group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Category name: The name used to represent the category. A category can have one name for every language that is activated in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: Low, Medium, High. The pre-defined priority of a category. Can be overridden by the person who fills out the message form. The priority of a message is the highest priority of the checked categories unless it is overridden by the user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cost: The predefined cost of a category. Can be overridden by the person who fills out the message form. The cost of a message is the sum of the costs of the checked categories, unless it is overridden by the user. Cost functionality can be removed for those who wish it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department: The category is available from the selected department and its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attached document: The document that will be activated if you click on the category in the message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information: Text field that is visible when you hold the cursor over the category in the message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Risk data: Appear only for the categories belonging to a category group with the category group type Risk. Used to set different acceptance criteria for various risk categories.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start yellow risk area: Overviews of this category will give a yellow risk value from (and including) this risk value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start the red risk area: Overviews of this category will give a red risk value from (and including) this risk value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add the category to the selected message forms (in the left column): In this panel you can manage the message forms to which the category will appear. The left panel shows the message forms where this category has already been added, the right panel shows the message forms where this category can be added. If a message form in the left panel is marked with yellow, the category will appear both when the message form is opened at the department where the category was added and at any subordinate department. Message forms in white will contain this category only when opening the form at the same department where the category was added. This is set by the state of the &amp;ldquo;Show for subdepartments&amp;rdquo; checkbox (checked or not) when adding the category to a message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes made in the fields.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 &amp;laquo; Add: Adds this category to the selected message form in the right panel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Remove &amp;raquo;: Removes this category from the selected message form in the left panel.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit category dependency</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/forms/functions/edit_category_dependency/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/forms/functions/edit_category_dependency/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;The headline of the page describes which category you edit the category dependencies for and which category group it belongs to. A category dependency is only used for the actual message form it was set up for. A category may only have one dependency against each of the other categories in that message form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A category satisfies its dependencies when it both:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;satisfies all &amp;ldquo;And&amp;rdquo; dependencies. If it has no &amp;ldquo;And&amp;rdquo; dependencies it is considered satisfied.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;satisfies at least one &amp;ldquo;Or&amp;rdquo; dependency or it has no &amp;ldquo;Or&amp;rdquo; dependencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that when you close this page you have to reload the page 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Categories or Edit message form for the changes to be visible in the category table. The easiest way to do that is by clicking on the tab 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Note.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Categories above the category table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The table Existing category dependencies shows the dependencies that the selected category already has (appears only if it has any). Here you can:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change the dependency type between &amp;ldquo;And&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Or&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delete a dependency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New category dependency. Here you can add a new dependency.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;First, select in the first drop-down menu the category group to which the category you want to set up a dependency on belongs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Then, select the category from the second drop-down menu. Note that the content of this menu depends on what you selected in the first drop-down menu.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finally, choose the dependency type. &amp;ldquo;And&amp;rdquo; is the default value.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Deletes the selected dependency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes done in the page. If the fields in the New category dependency part have been set, a new dependency is created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save for the group: Saves the changes done in the page. If the fields in the New category dependency part have been set, a new dependency is created and it is is added to all categories in the category group that appears in the headline of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Takes you back to the page where you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
