<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Tabs</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tabs on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Audit overview</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/audit_overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/audit_overview/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Shows a table with all the audits that the document has been through. Click on a row in the table to open the actual audit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit number. Identifier for the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information. Free text field with information entered by the audit responsible.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit responsible. The name of the user who is responsible for doing the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department. The name of the department where the audit was created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start date. The date when the audit starts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Due date. The due date for the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completed. The date when the audit was completed. Otherwise blank.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document content</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_content/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_content/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;These are documents that are written directly into Qm+ using its document editing tool. Opens from the page Edit document data.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TinyMCE is used to create the text editor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;spell-check&#34;&gt;Spell check&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If your browser has activated spell check, words that the spell checker considers to be misspelled will be highlighted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press the Ctrl key at the same time as you right click on the highlighted word to get spelling suggestions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;editor-buttons&#34;&gt;Editor buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The functions in this editor work in a similar way as in other document editing tools. Note in particular:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Bullist.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Bulleted (unordered) list: Select some text and click on this button to turn the text into a bulleted list. Click on the arrow to the right of the icon to select the bullet shape.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Numlist.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Numbered (ordered) list: Select some text and click on this button to turn the text into a numbered list. Click on the arrow to the right of the icon to select the number type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Outdent.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Decrease indent (outdent): Allows you to remove a &lt;tab&gt; character or combine a sub-list with the rest of the list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Indent.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Increase indent: Allows you to add a &lt;tab&gt; character or to create a sub-list of items in a list. For a sub-list the numbering starts anew. One can have different types of numbering in the list and the sub-list. This can be set using the arrow to the right of the Numbered list or the Bulleted list icon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Insert / Edit link: Select some text and then click on this button to turn the text into a link. You will then see a dialogue box where the link address can be entered.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Unlink.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Remove link (unlink): Select an existing link and then click on this button to turn the link into plain text.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Html.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Edit HTML source code: Opens a separate window where the document&amp;rsquo;s HTML code can be edited directly. This should be done only if you know HTML. Remember to click on the Update button when you are finished editing the HTML code. For explanation of the various HTML tags look here: Overview of HTML elements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document data</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_data/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_data/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;document-name-and-type&#34;&gt;Document name and type&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: The name of the document. Can be up to 100 characters long.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information: Short text (up to 500 characters) with information about the document. This text appears as a tooltip when you hover over the document name in Info, in message forms and lists.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document type: Τhe type of this document.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a document: Used if you wish to create (write) a document directly in Qm+. The document is saved as an HTML document and has some formatting options. The text edit field uses TinyMCE.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Link: Used if you wish to link to a resource on the internet or to a document on a local file server. Documents that are not accessible from the internet will not be indexed in our search engine and will appear as a Link Error under Documents. Make sure that the address entered is a valid http or https address.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;File: Used if you want to upload a file from your local computer to the Qm+ server. This creates a copy of the file on the server. To make changes in the file, it must be edited locally and then uploaded again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Folder: Used to create a folder structure under Info. Can not be opened as a document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Process chart: Used when you want to create a process chart in Qm+. When you save a document with this type, the tab Process chart setup becomes available and you are no longer able to change the document type of this document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;choose-where-the-document-will-be-shown-under-info&#34;&gt;Choose where the document will be shown under INFO&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document departments. Table that shows the departments where the document will be shown.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From department. The document will be visible under Info and under Admin / Documents on the departments that will be set here. Use the &amp;ldquo;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Add department&amp;rdquo; button to get a new drop-down menu in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shown for subdepartments. If this is checked, the document will also be visible under Info from the subdepartments of the department which is selected in the &amp;ldquo;From department&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Delete. Only active if the document is associated with more than one department. Click on the Delete department icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to delete the association with the specific department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tab: Determines under which tab the document will appear under Info. Mandatory field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document group: The document&amp;rsquo;s group. Determines in which box the document will appear under Info. Mandatory field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subdocument of: A subdocument will not be shown under Info, until the document above it is expanded by holding the cursor over the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Public document: If this is checked, the document will be available to everyone and no authentication will be required to open it. Applies only to documents of type &amp;ldquo;Write a document&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Link&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;File&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Position: Used only if the alphabetical sorting is turned off. Normally you can ignore this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;customer-specific-document-heading-fields&#34;&gt;Customer specific document heading fields&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These fields must be ordered separately. Used to add extra fields that will be displayed in the document heading. Only applicable for documents written in Qm+. Possible field types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Free text.
Date.
Department. Displays a drop-down menu that contains all departments. This may be role filtered, which means that only departments with a predefined role will be shown.
User. Displays a drop-down menu that contains all users. This may be role filtered, which means that only users with a predefined role will be shown.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;status&#34;&gt;Status&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This section appears only for documents that have been saved at least once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version: The version of the document. Displayed as x.y, where x is the main version number and y is the edit number.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The main version number is increased by 1 each time the button &amp;ldquo;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Disc_multiple.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create new version&amp;rdquo; is pressed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The edit number is increased by 1 each time this page is saved and either the name, the document content if this is a document written in Qm+, or the document address has changed or a new document has been uploaded.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The edit number starts at 1 for each new version that is created. The edit number in previous versions of Qm+ was referred to as the revision number.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The version number is displayed as a link that you can click on. It opens the document in that version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If the version shown on the page is newer than the published version of the document or the document has never been published, the button 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_lightning.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Publish will appear. This button stores any changes made in the document and sets the current version as the published one.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you are in a version of a document which has a newer version, you will be notified by the icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Exclamation.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and the text &amp;ldquo;This document has a newer version&amp;rdquo;. This text is a link that opens the newer version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documents that have a newer version can be changed, but you cannot create new versions of them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Published version. If the version of the document which is shown on the page is the actual published version, i.e. the one that appears under Info, the text &amp;ldquo;This is the published version&amp;rdquo; shows. If not, the version number of the actual published version of the document is displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created by: The name of the user who has created this document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latest edit by: The name of the user who changed the document last.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing status for this version: Appears only if the selected version is associated with a hearing. Displays the status of the hearing and links to Reply to a hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document address: Only shown for saved documents. If you want another document in Qm+ to refer to this document, you may use this address as a link. This address can now also be used outside Qm+ and, for documents written in Qm+ (Document type: Write a document) or for uploaded files (Document type: File), it will always take you to the latest published version. If you are not already logged into Qm+, you will be prompted for your username and password in order to see the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;audit&#34;&gt;Audit&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activate regular audit. You should check this when you want a user to be warned on a regular basis that the document should be audited. The following fields described in this section are shown when this box is checked.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Warning date for audit. The date when the user will be notified of the audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit interval. The period between each warning. When a document, for which the audit due date has passed, is audited, the warning date is increased by the value in this field. If the document gets audited before the audit due date, the warning date will not be automatically updated. If you wish to update the warning date in this case, you will have to do so manually.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit responsible. The user who receives the document audit warning in his / her Inbox.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;extra-attributes&#34;&gt;Extra attributes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document is a template. Yes / No. Standard No. Only applicable for documents of the type &amp;ldquo;Write a document&amp;rdquo;. A template document is an outline or start of a document, such as a set of standard headlines. Template documents that are saved and published can be inserted into, preferably new, documents from the Document content tab by all users. Template documents do not show under Info.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document heading type. Appears only for those who have the option for selectable document heading type set. Applies only to documents of the type &amp;ldquo;Write a document.&amp;rdquo; Determines which of the available document heading types will be used for this document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document groups</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_groups/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_groups/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here one can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s document groups.
Deactivated document groups do not appear under Info and no document can be assigned to them. Documents that belong to a deactivated document group do not appear under Info either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choice of department: The table shows either all the document groups created at the department which is selected in the Navigator or the document groups created at the department which is selected in the Navigator and those created by its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New document group: Opens the Edit document group screen to create a new document group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the Edit document group screen to change an existing document group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Deactivates or activates the document group depending on whether you are under Document groups or under Deactivated document groups respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Document tabs</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/document_tabs/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here one can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s document tabs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deactivated document tabs do not appear under Info and no documents can be assigned to them. Documents that belong to a deactivated document tab do not appear under Info either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New document tab: Opens the Edit document tab screen to create a new document tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Opens the Edit document tab screen to edit an existing document tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Deactivates or activates the document tab depending on whether you are under Document tabs or Deactivated document tabs respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/View.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Used to open a document tab which you do not have the right to change. One has the right to change the document tabs created from the selected department in the Navigator and the underlying departments of that&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Documents submenu</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/documents_submenu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/documents_submenu/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;From here you can manage the company&amp;rsquo;s documents.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The document names function as links. Click on a document name to open the document. Especially for documents created in Qm+: You can either open the HTML version by clicking on the document name, or you can get a PDF version of the document by clicking on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon on the right of the document name.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Deactivated documents do not appear under Info and cannot be attached to lists, message forms or activities. Already attached documents will still be shown there even if they are deactivated. Attached documents can not be deleted. Unpublished documents are not shown under Info either. If a document has both a published and a newer unpublished version, the published version will be displayed under Info.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes1hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create a new document click the button &amp;ldquo;New document&amp;rdquo; at the bottom of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit a document / send it out on a hearing: Click on the yellow &amp;ldquo;Edit document data&amp;rdquo;-icon on the right side of the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the next page you can select between the tabs Version overview, Hearing overview, Audit overview.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department selection: The table shows either all the documents created at the department which is selected in the Navigator or the documents created at the department which is selected in the Navigator and those from its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tab selection: The table shows only the documents that belong to the selected document tab. If the option &amp;ldquo;Show documents from all document tabs&amp;rdquo; is selected, all the documents are shown independent of the document tab they belong to. Please note that only documents that belong to active document tabs are shown. The drop-down does not contain any deactivated document tabs either, but contains tabs from all departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document group selection: The table shows only the documents that belong to the selected document group. If the option &amp;ldquo;Show documents from all document groups&amp;rdquo; is selected, all the documents are shown independent of the document group they belong to. Please note that only documents that belong to active document groups are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display mode:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document Information. Default, shows an overview of where in the structure the document belongs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Audit information. Displays the warning date for the next audit for the document and information about the previous / ongoing audit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New document: Opens the Edit document data screen to create a new document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;icons&#34;&gt;Icons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Icons are used to symbolize different types of documents:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_world.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Link to the online version of the document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Lovdata_icon.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Link to a page from Lovdata&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_word.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Word document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 PDF document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_excel.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Excel document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_powerpoint.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Powerpoint document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_text.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Document created in Qm+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Shape_align_center.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Document of type Process chart, created in Qm+&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Unknown or Blank document&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder_page_white.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Folder. Can not be opened, used only to create a document structure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;edit&#34;&gt;Edit&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Edit document data. Opens the Edit document data screen to edit an existing document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Date_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Create read and understood activity. This opens the New activity page under Activity plan and automatically sets the Activity group, the Activity name, the Attached list, the time period (From - To), the Activity distribution and the attached document. It is possible to use other lists than the default one for Read and understood. If someone wants to use another list as default, they will have to contact QmPlus AS. If you click the Create read and understood activity button of a document that has subdocuments, the subdocuments will also be added to the activity automatically.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Turnarrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Deactivate / Activate document. Deactivates or activates the document depending on whether you are under Documents or Deactivated documents respectively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Delete document. Deletes the document. Only visible for deactivated documents that are not attached to other elements in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;status&#34;&gt;Status&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_error.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Not indexed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_medal.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tag_blue_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: On hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Ok.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Error.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: Indexing error. This may mean that the document is not available or is in a format that our indexing engine has not been able to decipher. It may happen that even normal formats like .pdf and .doc fail. If the link opens the document correctly, the error only means that the document will not appear in any search results if you do a free text search under Info. Links to intranet pages or other sites that the search engine has no access to, will always give indexing errors.
Note: The symbol § in a link is often not recognised by the search engine, which leads to an indexing error. We suggest replacing it with its equivalent HTML code, which is %C2%A7.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Exclamation.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: The document has a newer unpublished / existing published version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Date.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


: The document is part of a Read and understood activity. If you leave the cursor over the icon, you will see a popup with information about the last Read and understood activity for the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Hearing / Approval</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/hearing_approval/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/hearing_approval/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here you can create a hearing, set its participants and approver.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing number: Serial number for all hearings in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Can have the values On hearing, For approval and Approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The hearing refers to document number X in version Y: Explains which document, in which version, the selected hearing applies to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document: Link to open the document itself.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the hearing: The person who has created the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created: The creation date and time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing due date: Deadline to reply to the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for approval of the document: The person who will approve the hearing and who can change its status. This field is mandatory.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants: The tool to determine who should participate in the hearing. Those taking part are in the left panel with the headline participants. They can be selected from the list in the right panel with the heading Choose participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send a comment by e-mail to the participants in the hearing: Here you can write a comment. When you click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save button, it will be sent as an e-mail to all listed under Participants.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comments to the hearing: Shows all comments that have come to this hearing. The comments can be sent from this page or from the page Reply to a hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/User.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 &amp;laquo;: Add participant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/User.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 &amp;raquo;: Remove participant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Telephone_link.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New hearing: Creates a new hearing for the selected version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes you have done in this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes this page and takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the active window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Process chart setup</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/process_chart_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/process_chart_setup/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Opens from the page Edit document data and shows only when the document type &amp;ldquo;Process chart&amp;rdquo; is selected and the document has been saved at least once.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This page is separated in two parts. The left part is the Tree structure of the process while the right one depends on what is selected in the left part. Please note that you can right click on the tree for more options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;general&#34;&gt;General&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new process initially has the same name as the document it contains it, but you can change it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can make a process chart in all the languages available in the system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, a process can contain steps (which have to be implemented in a certain order) or tasks (which do not have to be implemented in an order, they could also be done in parallel), but not both at the same level. By default, a new process contains 4 main steps. In the process chart Preview page, steps are depicted in yellow while tasks are depicted in light blue. We will use the general term phase for both steps and tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each step or task can have one or more responsible parties, which can be of type Object (User, Role, User type, Department) or Text (free text field with a limited size).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each step or task can have attributes (even if it is also a process with subprocesses). Attributes can be of type Object (User, Role, User type, Message form, Document, Department), Text (free text field with a limited size), Note (the Note field gives the possibility to write a longer text).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;how-to-set-up-a-process-chart&#34;&gt;How to set up a process chart&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After you have created a new document of type Process chart and filled in the related data in the Document data tab, you should click Save. That makes the Process chart setup tab appear. When you first click on the Process chart setup tab, the system automatically creates a process with the same name as the newly created document and 4 main steps. You can see that in the left part of the page in a Tree structure. Every time you click on a phase in the Tree, the page on the right is updated with the options related to the phase you selected in the Tree. You can also right click on a phase in the tree to get the same or (sometimes) additional options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;editing-the-main-process&#34;&gt;Editing the main process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes0hbhb-language-settings&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Keyboard.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Language settings&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here you can see a list with the available languages for your company. You should select in which of those the process chart will be available, and give the process name in all of them. The languages you select here will apply to the whole process chart. By default, the default language of the company and the current user&amp;rsquo;s language will be preselected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes1hbhb-configure-responsibilities&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_gear.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Configure responsibilities&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here you can select which of the available responsibilities will be used for this process chart. Select those you want from the list on the left and then click the Add button. The responsibilities you select here will appear in the Responsibility overview table on the right side of the page and will apply to the whole process chart. If you need to make a new responsibility for this chart that has not yet been defined in the system, you can click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New responsibility button. That will take you to the Responsibilities tab where you can define the new responsibility. After you do that and click Save and Close, you will be redirected back to this page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;set-default-attribute-type&#34;&gt;Set default attribute type&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here you can see a list with the available attribute types. The type you select here will come up as the first suggested option every time you try to add a new attribute to a sub phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;responsibility-overview&#34;&gt;Responsibility overview&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This table shows all the responsibilities that are available to the whole process and were selected via the Configure responsibilities button. You can remove a reponsibility by clicking on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;phases-with-linked-prosess-charts&#34;&gt;Phases with linked prosess charts&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This table appears if the process contains any phases with links to other processes. You can edit or remove a linked process chart by clicking on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 or the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 icon respectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;editing-a-phase&#34;&gt;Editing a phase&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes6hbhb-add-step&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Stepimage.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Add step&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here you are required to write the name of the step in all the languages you selected in the Language settings window earlier. You can also select the position, which is the order in which this step needs to be done within its parent phase. This button appears when the selected phase has no children of type task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please note: By default, the main process has 4 main steps to which you can add more if you wish by clicking on this button. If your process is to be comprised of tasks instead of steps, you will need to delete the default steps one by one by right clicking on their names on the tree and selecting Delete from the available options. Then the Add task button will also appear.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes7hbhb-add-task&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Taskimage.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Add task&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This button appears when the selected phase has no children of type step. Here you are required to write the name of the task in all the languages you selected in the Language settings window earlier. You can also select the position, which will only affect where this task will be shown in the tree structure underneath its parent phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes8hbhb-convert-to-step&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Stepimage.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Convert to step&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This button appears only for tasks. It gives you the possibility to change this task and all other tasks in the same level to steps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes9hbhb-convert-to-task&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Taskimage.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Convert to task&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This button appears only for steps. It gives you the possibility to change this step and all other steps in the same level to tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes10hbhb-import-process-chart&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Shape_align_center.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Import process chart&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This button appears when the selected phase has no children. Here you have the option to select another process chart from the system and import it under the selected phase. This will copy that process inside the current document, which you will be able to see immediately in the tree structure on the left. Any changes done to the original chart after the import will not affect the current process chart. You will also get the option to &amp;ldquo;Replace name with imported process name&amp;rdquo;. If you select this, the name of the selected phase will be replaced by the name of the top level process in the imported chart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes11hbhb-link-to-process-chart&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Shape_align_center.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Link to process chart&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This button appears when the selected phase has no children. Here you have the option to select another process chart from the system and link it under the selected phase. This will NOT copy that process inside the current document, it will only make a direct link to it. You will not be able to see the structure of the linked process chart in the tree structure on the left, you will only see a link symbol on the selected step 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Icon_step_linked.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 or task 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Icon_task_linked.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


. The linked process will appear normally in the Process chart view page. Any changes done to the original chart after the linking will have an immediate effect on the current process chart. After you link the selected phase to another process chart, you will be able to edit or remove that link if needed using the icons 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 respectively inside the linked process table that will appear at the bottom of the page for the selected phase or from the same table that will appear at the bottom of the page of the top level phase of this process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;edit&#34;&gt;Edit&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This option comes up when you right click on a phase in the Tree, and gives the same options that appear on the right side of the page when you left click on the name of a phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;delete&#34;&gt;Delete&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This option comes up only when you right click on a phase in the Tree. If the phase that you are trying to delete has children, you will be informed of how many child nodes it has and you will be asked if you want to delete them all together with the selected phase or if you want to move them under a new parent node and which one. Otherwise, you will only get a confirmation message before actually deleting the selected phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;change-parent&#34;&gt;Change parent&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This option comes up when you right click on a phase in the Tree. It gives you the possibility to move the selected phase by selecting a new parent node for it. You can move it under any other phase that has no other children or that has children of the same type as the one you are trying to move (steps or tasks).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;add-responsible&#34;&gt;Add responsible&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here you can select who will be responsible for the selected phase with what kind of responsibility. You can set multiple responsible parties for a phase. First you select the responsibility (from the responsibilities configured on the main process level). You can write the responsible in a free text field (in all the languages set up on the main process level) or select from one of the available qm+ objects, User, Role, User type and Department. After you select the Object type you can also select its value from the list below. All responsible parties that you will set here will appear in a table below the button. You can later edit or delete a responsible using the respective icons 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;add-attribute&#34;&gt;Add attribute&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here you can add more attributes to the phase. First you select the type of the attribute (first option is the Default attribute type configured on the main process level). The available types are:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Object: User, Role, User type, Message form, Document, Department (dependent on the department which is selected in the Navigator). If there is a selected Department here, we will use this node as the starting point when displaying the chart display page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Text: free text field with a limited size (50 characters).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Note: The Note field gives the possibility to write a longer text (255 characters). In the diagram, only a note mark is shown in the attribute list, while the note itself is displayed outside the figure at the bottom of the page in a separate Notes table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can also select the position, which is the order in which this attribute will show within its phase (compared to the other attributes, if any).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All attributes that you will set here will appear in the Attributes table below the button. You can later edit or delete an attribute using the respective icons 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Group_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;display-modes&#34;&gt;Display modes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A document of type Process chart can be displayed in two modes, 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Shape_align_center.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Process chart (the graphical representation of the process) and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_side_tree.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Responsibility matrix (if any responsible parties have been defined). Both of these buttons are at the bottom of the page and open a new window. You can only have one of these views open at a time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the document is opened, it will automatically get a meta-table that contains data about the document, identical to the one added to documents of type Written document.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Both views of the document can be exported to a .pdf file. Clicking on the Show as pdf button takes you to the page Option page for process reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;process-chart-view&#34;&gt;Process chart view&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The name of the process is shown above the chart at the center. Steps are represented by yellow boxes and are connected to their parent phase with black arrows, while tasks are represented by light blue boxes and are connected to their parent phase with blue lines. The phase (step or task) name is shown in bold inside the box, at the top.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the upper right part of the page, you can see the Display settings for the whole chart, all of which start preselected. Please note that if you click on the Show as pdf button, the report will contain the same chart that is shown in this window, based on the selected display settings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show responsibles: The responsible parties for each phase are shown in a red font below the phase name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show attributes:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attributes of type Message form are shown in a blue font, and have the icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Application_form_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 in front. By clicking on the form name this window closes and you are taken to the page where you can register a message using that message form. When you save and / or close that page you will be taken back to the Process chart set up page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attributes of type Document are shown in a blue font, and have the icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 in front. If you click on the document name, the document will open in a separate window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attributes of type Note are shown in a black font, and they only appear as &amp;ldquo;Note1&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Note 2&amp;rdquo; etc inside a phase. These are clickable and take you to the aggregated Notes table which appears below the chart and contains the various phases that contain Notes attributes and the text written inside each Note.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All other types of attributes are shown in a black font.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display full chart: Displays the full chart. If this is not selected, then only the phases of the first level are shown in the chart. When you move the mouse cursor over the various phase names, it changes to the hand cursor if the phase is clickable, which means that it has children. Clicking on the phase name or in the empty space inside the phase expands the tree below it by one level.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;responsibility-matrix-view&#34;&gt;Responsibility matrix view&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If at least one responsible has been defined for a phase of the process, then the process chart can also be displayed in a matrix format that lists all the phases of the process in the first column in a hierarchical structure and the responsible parties in the first row. Inside the matrix, the responsibility codes are shown. If a phase has a Document attribute, the icon 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 will appear next to the phase name. You can click on it to see the name of that document which is also a a hyperlink, and clicking on it opens the document in a separate window. Below the responsibility matrix is the Responsibility overview table, which explains the Responsibilities (codes, names, additional information) that are available for this process.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Read and understood</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/read_and_understood/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/read_and_understood/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Here you can see an overview of the status of all Read and understood activities the document has had.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table-headings&#34;&gt;Table headings&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Period: Shows the time period during which the activity was active.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: The name of the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created by: The name of the user who created the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reference: If the activity is set up with a reference, the link to the reference is displayed here.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completed forms: The participation in the activity is shown in a small bar chart as the number of answers / the number of possible participants.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For common activities, the numbers after the bar chart represent the number of users who answered / the number of users who will participate in the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For repetitive activities, the numbers after the bar chart represent the number of users who answered / number users who can participate / the total number of answers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comments: The number of comments on this activity. Opens the page Comments to the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email reminder: Here you can send out the activity as an e-mail to those who have to perform it. Send reminder is also used when you want to warn the users who have not filled out the activity. Opens the Send reminder in a separate window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer form: Appears only for the current activities that have already started.Here you can fill out the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Result: Here you get the result from the activity. Opens the page Graphs for the list.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Date_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create read and understood activity: This opens the New activity page under Activity plan and automatically sets the Activity group, the Activity name, the Attached list, the time period (From - To), the Activity distribution and the attached document. It is possible to use other lists than the default one for Read and understood. If someone wants to use another list as default, they will have to contact QmPlus AS. If you click the Create read and understood activity button of a document that has subdocuments, the subdocuments will also be added to the activity automatically.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Disc_multiple.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create new version: Creates a new version of the document.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Example: If a document is in version 3.14 and you click on this button, it will change version to 4.1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Should be used before making major changes to the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shows only for documents that have been saved at least once.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes you have done in this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes this page and takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the active window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Reference overview</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/reference_overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/reference_overview/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Shows a table with all the documents that refer to (contain an image or link reference to) the current document.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If the document is of type &amp;ldquo;Written document&amp;rdquo; then a second table shows the documents that this document refers to in its content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reference type. Image 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Image.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 or Link 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name. The document name. The table is sorted by this column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Department. The departments this document has been added to. If the document is from the common library, then this is written here instead of a department name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subdocument of.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document group.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document tab.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit. If the user has access rights to edit the specific document, the relevant icons appear.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Reply to a hearing</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/reply_to_hearing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/reply_to_hearing/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page can be accessed from the Inbox of those who should reply to it, and from Edit document data under Admin / Documents for users with access to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This page is used for replying to a hearing. The users who have been given the responsibility to participate in the hearing can reply to it and give their comments. The hearing&amp;rsquo;s status can be changed by the person who has been assigned the responsibility to approve it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document: Link to open the document itself. Document number X in version Y: Number (X) and version (Y) of the document to which the hearing is attached. 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Link_edit.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 takes you to the Edit document data page for that document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for approval of the document: The person who will approve the hearing and who can change its status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing / approval status: Can have the values On hearing, For approval and Approved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing number: Serial number for all hearings in the system.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created: The creation date of the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the hearing: The person who has created the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing due date: The deadline (date and time) to reply to the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My answer to the hearing: Unanswered / Ok / Not ok. Used by those who will participate in the hearing to provide feedback on the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hearing / approval status drop-down: Used by the person responsible for approving the hearing to change its status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comment: Text field that can be used by anyone with access to the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My comment: Menu for selecting who will receive the message written in the Comment field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes you have made in this screen. If you wrote a comment it will be sent in the manner you have chosen in My answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes this page and takes you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tables&#34;&gt;Tables&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants in the hearing: Overview over those who will reply to the hearing, their answers and when they last changed their answer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comments to the hearing: All comments added to the hearing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Version overview</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/version_overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/document/tabs/version_overview/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Used to provide an overview of all the versions of the document.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The table contains one row per version (Major version) that the document has been through.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Name: Name of the document for this version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version: &amp;ldquo;Version number.Edit number&amp;rdquo;. Create a new version when you have made ​​major changes to the document. Must be done manually. The edit number changes whenever you save a change in the document.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to show the minor versions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The version that is published and displayed under Info is marked with a 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_put.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Copy and set as latest version. Click on this to copy the version of this row as a new version. Copies all content and document data, including the name. Shows only for documents of type Written document (&amp;ldquo;Write a file&amp;rdquo;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Address: The address of the document. Click on it to open the selected version of the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created by: Who created this version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created: When this version was first created.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latest edit by: The last user to change the document.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Latest edit: When the last change was made.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compare: You can select any 2 versions from the table. Then when you click the Compare versions button, you will be able to see the text or the HTML differences between the two versions. Use the Compare as HTML / Compare as text button to switch the comparison view mode. Added elements are highlighted with green, while removed elements are highlighted with red and a strikethrough line. The function works only for documents written in the Qm+ editor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
