<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Tabs</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tabs on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Dialog</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/dialog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/dialog/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;fields&#34;&gt;Fields&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: The status of the message and who is responsible for it, are shown at the top of the page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feedback to case handler: Here you can write a text and send it by email. The sent text will also be registered on the case and will follow it. It will appear in this screen in the table below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send email to: Select the person who should receive the message. The list is sorted by department and includes:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The nearest manager(s) is (are) always displayed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The current case handler of the selected message, if one has been set.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anyone who has sent a message to the logged in user about the specific case.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A table that shows the previous communication on this issue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Edit message</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/edit_message/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/edit_message/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;A message form has checkboxes or drop-down menus and text fields specified by the company&amp;rsquo;s super user. At least one field will have an orange-like background colour. Orange fields are mandatory and must be filled out so that the message can be saved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When a message is saved, it is registered on the department that is written in the top of the middle column in the message form. The message will appear immediately in the Inbox of the person(s) that is defined as the manager of the selected department, unless the early case process is enabled, see below. The message will also appear immediately under Reports and in the reports created from the same or a subordinate department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;filling-out-the-form&#34;&gt;Filling out the form&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remember to check something in all the fields with an orange-like background colour. There will usually be one such field in the upper left part of the screen. You will get an error message if you try to save a message and there are mandatory fields that have not been filled out. Please note that if there are more than one fields marked with 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tag_blue.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


, you will only be able to select one category from all of them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Checkboxes:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Single choice: Fields that have a round box in front of each option. That means that you can select one option in this group. Once you have selected one option in a single choice field, then you can not take it away again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multiple choice: Fields that have a square box in front of each option. Here you can check any number alternatives or none at all.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Check boxes and enter text in the fields you feel that apply to you. It may be that some message forms are general and that only some fields are relevant in your situation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remember that the person who handles your message can make changes, typically write down additional information and change the cost field and priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If there is a suggestion field, type your suggestion there. It is important for the improving process of the business. Some companies reward the month&amp;rsquo;s or half the year&amp;rsquo;s best suggestions for improvement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: This field gets a value based on the selections you make in the message form. This value can be overridden.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cost: This field is meant to represent the actual cost of the registered message. This field gets a value based on the selections you make in the message form. This value can be overwritten. Super users can remove the cost field from a message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Risk assessment: Some message forms may have a built-in risk assessment. In some cases, you should then evaluate the probability and the consequence that the registered event will happen again, in other cases you should evaluate the probability and the consequence for a hypothetical event. The risk value is then automatically calculated and displayed with a colour at the corresponding location in the risk matrix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Numeric fields: Categories can be displayed as numeric fields instead of checkboxes. Such numeric fields can be used to report for example the number of liters of water consumption or other number or quantity statements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload file: Use this if you want to add external files to the message, like images etc. Maximum file size allowed is 10 MB. Not enabled in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save / Send: Saves the changes you have done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Folder_table.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Process: Only for users having the process message system role. Saves the changes you have done and takes you to the Message process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_copy.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Copy: Copies this message and opens the copy. Appears only for risk messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports from which you can export the current message to a .pdf file. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Sends you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Change message form: Only for users having the system role Content Administrator. Gives the possibility to change the message form of a message. It only shows how the current message would look if another form was used. The message form is not actually changed until the user presses the Save button. Anonymity, department, priority, text fields, cost fields and any selected categories that are common in both message forms (the one used for the original message and the new one) are preserved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Version overview: Only for saved messages. The latest version is always selected when the message opens. Any other previous version can be selected. Then the message will be shown as it appeared at that time. You can only make changes to the latest version. All changes to a message lead to the creation of a new version. New versions are marked with who made the change and when.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered on department: Only for users with the system role Content administrator. Used for moving registered messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;early-case-process&#34;&gt;Early case process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This field appears only for messages that are not saved and only if it is enabled for the message form you are looking at. Activation of Early case process is not recommended for new customers unless they have special requirements.
Early case process means that the message can be assigned to a responsible person already when it is being registered. Normally this is not done by the person who registers the message but only when a manager or case handler is processing the case on the department where the message was registered. The Early case process can be activated by users with user type Manager on the top department or by users who have the system role Content administrator. This can be done under Admin / Rules, Rule type &amp;ldquo;Early case handlers&amp;rdquo; if you create such a rule for a message form. It is also possible to activate an option that shows a menu in the New message page similar to the &amp;ldquo;Send to case handler&amp;rdquo; drop-down in the Message process page. With this option you do not need &amp;ldquo;Early case handler&amp;rdquo; rules, but they can be used even if this option is on and the drop-down menu in the New message page will only show those.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send to case handler / line manager: Drop-down menu where you can choose to whom this message will be sent. This does not change the department on which the message is registered, even if the selected user is in another department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send email: If this is checked here, an email will be sent to the selected user when you press the Save button.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deadline: Date / Time. This date and time will appear as the deadline for those who will receive the message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;tabs&#34;&gt;Tabs&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The tabs here are only active for saved messages. Changes made in the page will not be saved if you click on a tab.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit message: Reloads the message. Use this if you want to remove the changes you have made and have not saved yet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dialog: For simplified interface. Takes you to the Dialog screen.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message process: For user types having the complete interface. Takes you to the Message process page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Message process</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/message_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/message_process/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Used for processing messages. Notice the message status. It can be seen both in the header and in the message field below. Also note whether the case currently has a responsible person before you start doing something about it. If it does, it is written in the field &amp;ldquo;Current case handler: &lt;user name&gt;&amp;rdquo; just below the header.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;hahahugoshortcodes0hbhb-what-can-i-do-here&#34;&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Info.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 What can I do here?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Here I can handle a case. Click: Choose action in the yellow / orange panel, or&amp;hellip;..&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can simply &amp;ldquo;Send a note about the case&amp;rdquo;. Click on the white checkbox and write in the textfield that appears. This is sent by e-mail!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can also edit the message contents: Click on the tab &amp;ldquo;Edit message&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;message-details&#34;&gt;Message details&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This table provides a brief description of the content and status of the message that will be processed in this page. Click on 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to see the rest of the checked categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;choose-action&#34;&gt;Choose action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drop-down menu with a coloured background that means that this is where you need to do something if you come to this page. Whatever choice you make in this drop-down menu, you will be able to check off the &amp;ldquo;Send a note about the case&amp;rdquo; that makes the dialog boxes appear and gives you the possibility to send an email to those involved in the case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Possible actions: Click Save / Send after you have selected an action in order for it to happen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose case handler: Used when you want to transfer the responsibility for the message to someone else, or set a deadline for the message. Note that it is up to the receiver of the message whether (s)he will create an action or (s)he will reject it. Those you can send the message to are those who have the user type manager or case handler on your own department, the department above it in the hierarchy or one of the departments under your own. You can also send the message to those who are set up under the tab Rules with the rule type &amp;ldquo;Additional case handlers&amp;rdquo; with a remit that includes your department. Please note that for messages that are created with message forms which have a role with the &amp;ldquo;See messages&amp;rdquo; limitation, those who do not satisfy that limitation will be taken off this list. You can set a deadline for when the person you send it to should have done something about it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to former case handler: Used when you want to transfer the responsibility for the message back to someone who had it before. This option is only shown when a message has changed case handler at least once.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reject: Used when a message will not be followed up further. This may be a test message, or duplicate or similar. This option should not be used for real messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Register done action&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Close the case. Used when a small action that does not require further action is about to be executed or has already been executed. You get the opportunity to register who has executed the action and write a name and a description of the work that was done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan an action: Opens all the fields for the planning phase of the action.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give the action a name.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a description of the work that will be performed. This must contain enough information, so that the person who will be assigned to the job will know what to do. You can also give an extended description of what can be done to prevent the incident from happening again.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose who will perform the action in the field &amp;ldquo;Choose the persons that will do the job&amp;rdquo;. If you need people from other departments, use the department selection drop-down menu above the two fields that show the users. To add users, select them in the right panel and press the &amp;laquo; button.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Update the deadline (&amp;ldquo;Must be finished before&amp;rdquo;) if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send email to those who are responsible for the execution if necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Click Save / Send. This will create the action. A link to the new action appears in a table at the top of the page. Click on it or on the tab Action process if you wish to see the complete action details.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload file: Used to upload external files that will be attached to this message. Maximum file size is 10 MB. Not enabled in the standard version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send to Facilit. Appears only for those who have integration with Facilit. Select a property and a building and press Save. This creates an action in Qm+ that is attached to an action in Facilit. The text and the categories from the original deviation are also sent to the action in Facilit. When the action in Facilit changes status, the status of the action in Qm+ is updated also. No other information from Facilit appears in the action in Qm+ other than the status change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is an option there, where, on a customer basis, one can choose if an action that is reported to be completed in Facilit should get the status Under approval (default) or Approved. An action that gets the status Under approval in Qm+ must be approved manually in Qm+ by the person who sent the case to Facilit in order to close it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Each customer has the option to remove all options from this drop-down menu except from &amp;ldquo;Close the case&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Reject&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;send-a-note-about-the-case&#34;&gt;Send a note about the case&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This field is used to send text messages to users who are involved in the case. Anyone who has access to a message can use these fields, regardless of the message&amp;rsquo;s status. All notes sent here will be saved in this case and shown in the &amp;ldquo;Case history&amp;rdquo; table at the bottom of the page. They are also sent as an email if the selected recipients have registered a valid email address. If the SMS-module is activated, the option to send the notification as an SMS also appears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message originator (&amp;ldquo;Registered on behalf of&amp;rdquo;): Check this box to send a text message to the person who originally created the message. The name of this user is in the field &amp;ldquo;Registered on behalf of&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Has the case now: Field for the current case handler.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Former case handlers: Field for all the users who have been responsible for the message previously. Select the person(s) you want to send a message to.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inform more: Here you can select users who are not directly involved in the case but should nevertheless be informed about it. The users in the left panel will receive the message you wrote when you press Save.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Choose from: Drop-down menu that determines which users will appear in the list of potential recipients to the right below this menu. The options are:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Case handler list: All users with a user type containing the system role inform shortlist on the selected department in the Navigator, the department above it and in all departments below it in the hierarchy. In addition, all the users with the a user type containing the system role Process message that are set up under the tab Rules with a remit that includes the selected department in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All: All users, regardless of user type, from the department which is selected in the Navigator and its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;Role name&gt;: All users, regardless of user type, the department which is selected in the Navigator and its subordinate departments who have the selected role.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;There is an option there, where, on a customer basis, one can choose if the options All and &lt;Role name&gt; will show all users regardless of department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Tick.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Save: Saves the changes you have made. If the send email option was checked, this action sends the emails.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Email_go.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Send: Sends the message you wrote, but does not save any other changes. This button is shown in place of the Save button if you do not have edit rights to the message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/User_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 &amp;laquo;: Moves the selected users from the right panel to the recipient list on the left.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/User_add.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 &amp;laquo; All: Moves all the users from the right panel to the recipient list on the left.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/User_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 &amp;raquo; All: Removes all users from the recipient list. Those who belong to the selected list (list type set in the drop-down menu &amp;ldquo;Choose from:&amp;rdquo;) appear in the list on the right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/User_delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 &amp;raquo;: Removes the selected users from the recipient list. Those who belong to the selected list (list type set in the drop-down menu &amp;ldquo;Choose from:&amp;rdquo;) appear in the list on the right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Sends you back to the page you came from.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports from which you can export the current message to a .pdf file. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete (icon): Appears next to the attachment hyperlink. Used to delete attachments. Available only for the user who uploaded the attachment and for Content administrators.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Delete.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Delete (button): Appears at the bottom of the screen for messages with status Rejected and only for Content administrators. Marks a message as Deleted. Such messages can only be found again by searching for the message number and require the system role Content administrator to be opened.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the active window.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;case-history&#34;&gt;Case history&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shows the history of all changes for the message, both for content and status. Shows also all correspondence about the case. All messages sent from the dialog panel above and all replies sent to them are shown here.
Tabs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit message: Opens the Edit message page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message process: Reloads this page. All changes you have made but not saved will be lost.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Message search</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/message_search/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/message_search/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page is used for searching among registered messages. The initial value of the Form type field depends on which tab you opened this page from. In many cases it is more appropriate to use Reports to identify specific messages than to use this page, but this page gives more options. This page can also be used together with Reports via the Expand search button in the search results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;general-search-criteria&#34;&gt;General search criteria&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time frame: Search for cases from a certain time period. From and To date fields (inclusive).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Include messages with the selected status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Priority: Include messages with the selected priority.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form type: Appears only if the Log messages or the Risk messages are activated. Include messages with the selected form type. The result will appear in the tab corresponding to the selected form type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Form: Only messages created with the selected message form will be included. If you select something other than &amp;ldquo;All&amp;rdquo; here, the category groups and the categories in the section &amp;ldquo;Type of category to search by&amp;rdquo; below will only show those that are in use in the selected message form.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message number: Search for messages with the selected message number. When this field is used, none of the other search criteria is used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered on behalf of: Search for messages reported by the selected user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Content search: Search for messages containing a given text. The text can be in any of the text fields in the message. Characters are not case sensitive. Lucene is the search engine used for this function. See Lucene Query Syntax for detailed information about the syntax for the search field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show messages from:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This department: Only messages registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This and subordinate departments: All messages registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator and on its subordinate departments are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subordinate departments: Only messages registered on the subordinate departments of the one which is selected in the Navigator are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Risk: Show the messages with categories of the category group type Risk. Choose the P and C value for the messages that will be included in the search.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;P: Probability. Value from 0 - 5. 0 means that this parameter will not be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;C: Consequence. Value from 0 - 5. 0 means that this parameter will not be used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;type-of-category-to-search-by&#34;&gt;Type of category to search by&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This section is used to search for category groups and categories. Check one or more category groups and / or select categories from the menus. The defining category groups appear at the top. Among them you can only search for one category group and / or category. If a message type or a message form is selected, only the category groups and the categories used in these message forms will appear in this section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;order-by&#34;&gt;Order by&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Select the column by which the result table will be sorted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;show-results-in&#34;&gt;Show results in&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Table: Show the results in the table of the Search results page for messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expanded view: Show the results in the expanded view that contains all the message details (previously &amp;ldquo;Printer friendly&amp;rdquo; version) of the Search results page for messages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Graph: Show the result as a chart under Reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Message search results</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/message_search_result/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/message_search_result/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;This page displays the results when performing a message search and when someone has clicked on a message graph under Reports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;search-criteria&#34;&gt;Search criteria&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Displays all the parameters that are used for the search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drop-down menu Departments:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This department. Only messages registered on the selected department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This and subordinate departments. Messages registered on the selected department and on its subordinate departments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subordinate departments. Only messages registered on the subordinate departments of the selected department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that if the search criteria were set by clicking on a graph, the search can be based on a different department than the one selected in the Navigator. This department is shown in the field &amp;ldquo;Search from department&amp;rdquo; in the search criteria table. The Navigator can be used to change the selected department.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Find.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 New search: Opens the search page for messages with all the search parameters cleared, except from the department which is selected in the Navigator and the selected message type.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Find.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Expand search: Opens the search page for messages with all parameters listed in the search criteria list set. You should use this button if you want to continue working with the current search and edit some of the search criteria.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Chart_bar.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Back to the graphs: Opens the Reports as they appeared in the previous page. The bar on which you has clicked to open this page is not added to the search criteria. This button appears only if you opened this page by clicking on a graph under Reports. When you click on a graph under Reports you perform a search for the messages that were represented by the bar you clicked on.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Chart_bar.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show in graphs: Opens the Reports with the messages in the table below as the starting point. The bar on which you has clicked to open this page is added to the search criteria.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Use of the table is explained in Messages/NC, Log, Risk and Comments, depending on which tab you are under.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Sent to case handler</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/sent_to_casehandler/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/message/tabs/sent_to_casehandler/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;Sent to case handler shows all messages that have been transferred to a responsible person. This is used to find messages that you have sent away so that they are no longer available on your department. Which messages are shown in the table below is determined by the choices in the drop-down menus. Only messages registered in the last 3 months are shown in this screen. To see older messages, please use Reports or Search.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;functions&#34;&gt;Functions&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;drop-down-menus&#34;&gt;Drop-down menus&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All messages: If you select a message form, only messages originating in such a message form are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message type:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From a case handler in this department: Shows messages sent from a user on the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;From me: Shows messages sent by the logged in user.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To a case handler in this department: Shows messages that have been assigned to a responsible person from the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Registered on this department: Shows messages originally registered on the department which is selected in the Navigator.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Status: Only messages with the selected status are displayed in the table.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All states: All messages are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Message process: Only messages with the status New or Sent to case handler are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Action process: Only messages attached to an action that has not yet been approved are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rejected: Only rejected messages are shown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;table&#34;&gt;Table&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When you click on a line of the main table, the selected message will open in the handling page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold the cursor over the + symbol in the first column to get more information about a message, including its history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Expanded view / 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Table.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Table: Switch between the expanded and the table view. The table gives a compact description of messages intended for use when working with them. The expanded view gives a more complete description of the messages, similar to the printer friendly (.pdf) version.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Show as pdf: Opens the Option page for reports, from which you can create a report with the related messages. This is intended for paper printing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/LeftArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/RightArrow.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Change page: The arrows are used to change pages when there are more than 20 messages that can be shown in the table.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 and 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Sorting: The table is sorted by the column with the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowopen.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


. Click on the 

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Arrowclosed.gif&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 to sort by another column.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Printer.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Print: Prints the current page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
