<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quality Manager – Reports</title>
    <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reports on Quality Manager</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	  <atom:link href="https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
        
      
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Option page for process reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/option_page_process_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/option_page_process_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;options&#34;&gt;Options&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include document heading: Select this option if you want the automatically generated document heading to be included at the top of the report. Preselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include notes: Select this option if you want the notes table to be included at the bottom of the report (if the process has attributes of type Note). Preselected. Shows only in Process chart view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include responsibilities: Select this option if you want the Responsibility overview table to be included at the bottom of the report. Preselected. Shows only in Responsibility matrix view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Page size: You can select between A4, A3 and Automatic. If you select A4 or A3, the process chart will be automatically adjusted to fit in a single page of the selected size. If you select Automatic, the process chart will be displayed on a page that is adapted to its size. Shows only in Process chart view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Page orientation: You can select between Landscape and Portrait.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create report: Creates the report with the selected options. Please note that you should not close this page before the report is ready, otherwise you will never see the report. After the new report opens, you can either change the selected options and create another report (same data, perhaps different view) or simply close this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes the Option page for process reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Option page for reports</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/option_page_reports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/option_page_reports/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;h3 id=&#34;options&#34;&gt;Options&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;show-summary-report&#34;&gt;Show summary report&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This report will contain only some basic information about the messages or actions. The report will be similar to the table view from Archive. Shows only when coming from Archive or Comments to the activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the title: Select this option if you want the page title to be included in the report as its title. Preselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the company logo: Select this option if you want the company logo to be included at the upper left corner of the report. Not shown when .xls format is selected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the search criteria: Select this option if you want the search criteria to be included in the report above the results. Shows only if the search criteria were shown in the page where you came from. Preselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the risk table(s): Select this option if you want the risk table(s) to be included in the report above the results. Shows only if the same tables were shown in the page where you came from. Preselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;show-complete-report&#34;&gt;Show complete report&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This report will contain all available information about the messages or actions. The report will be similar to the Extended view from Archive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the title: Select this option if you want the page title to be included in the report as its title. Preselected when coming from Archive or Comments to the activity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the company logo: Select this option if you want the company logo to be included at the upper left corner of the report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the case history: Select this option if you want the case history to show below each message or action in the report. Preselected. If the option &amp;ldquo;Include the attached messages / actions&amp;rdquo; is selected, this will apply also to the attached cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hide the message originator: Select this option if you do not want the name of the message originators to appear in a message report. Shows only when the option &amp;ldquo;Include the case history&amp;rdquo; is not selected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the search criteria: Select this option if you want the search criteria to be included in the report above the results. Shows only if the search criteria were shown in the page where you came from. Preselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the risk table(s): Select this option if you want the risk table(s) to be included in the report above the results. Shows only if the same tables were shown in the page where you came from. Preselected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Disable risk colours in message list: Select this option if you do not wish to have any risk-related colours in the messages. Shows only when coming from Risk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the image attachments: Select this option if you want the image attachments to be included in the report. Supported image formats are: .png, .bmp, .jpg, .jpeg, .gif, .ico. Shows only for messages. Please note that image resizing is done automatically at this point. If you are experiencing problems with the images in the reports please send an email to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:katerina@qmplus.com&#34;&gt;katerina@qmplus.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the attached actions. Shows only for messages. Includes the actions for each message.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include the attached messages. Shows only for actions. Includes the messages for each action.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show one case per page: Select this option if you want to print each case on a separate page. If the option &amp;ldquo;Include the attached messages / actions&amp;rdquo; is selected, this will apply also to the attached cases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;exported-file-format&#34;&gt;Exported file format&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have the possibility to choose the exported file format (.pdf / .docx / .doc / .odt / .xls) for message or action reports. Please note that the .pdf version is the most suitable for printing. At this point, we cannot guarantee that the .docx / .doc version will look the same in all editors or that the documents will open correctly with all versions of Microsoft Office (works best with MS Word 2010) and OpenOffice. This export format should only be used when there is a need for manually editing the report.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;buttons&#34;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Page_white_acrobat.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Create report: Creates the report with the selected options. Please note that you should not close this page before the report is ready, otherwise you will never see the report. After the new report opens, you can either change the selected options and create another report (same data, perhaps different view) or simply close this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Cross.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Close: Closes the Option page for reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;

  &lt;img src=&#34;https://docs3.qmplus.com/images/Help.png&#34;  width=&#34;&#34; /&gt;


 Help: Opens this page.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docs: Tabs</title>
      <link>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs3.qmplus.com/en/docs/report/tabs/</guid>
      <description>
        
        
        &lt;p&gt;All tabs associated with reports.&lt;/p&gt;

      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
